<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tales of the weird on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/tales-of-the-weird/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tales of the weird on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/tales-of-the-weird/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Happy Saint Patrick&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/03/18/happy-saint-patricks-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/03/18/happy-saint-patricks-day/</guid>
      <description>To celebrate, here&amp;rsquo;s some awesomeness from Mobile, AL:
Leprechaun in Mobile, Alabama</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More burger news</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/11/more-burger-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/11/more-burger-news/</guid>
      <description>Ok, it&amp;rsquo;s not exactly news. But I&amp;rsquo;ve randomly run into some more food oddities. I say randomly because I ran across it on this guy&amp;rsquo;s del.icio.us bookmarks (he wrote Cocoalicious, a slick del.icio.us client for OS X). Anyway, here&amp;rsquo;s the link. Featured are the Luther Burger (a bacon cheeseburger served on a toasted Krispy Kreme bun) and the Hamdog (a hot dog wrapped in a beef patty that&amp;rsquo;s deep fried, covered with chili, cheese and onions, and served on a hoagie bun topped with a fried egg and two fistfuls of fries).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger news</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/10/burger-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/10/burger-news/</guid>
      <description>Amanda was telling me that the mayor of Detroit (who&amp;rsquo;s apparently assisted in creating a 300 million dollar deficit) has proposed an additional tax on fast-food to help fill the city&amp;rsquo;s coffers. Guess this is a strategic move since Detroit&amp;rsquo;s ranked third on the list of &amp;ldquo;fattest cities&amp;rdquo; (following Houston and Chicago)&amp;hellip;
On a related note, I saw this other article at CNN about a restaurant that&amp;rsquo;s started selling a 15-pound burger!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why am I not surprised...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/07/why-am-i-not-surprised/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/07/why-am-i-not-surprised/</guid>
      <description>Saw Power Tool Drag Racing recently on the Discovery Channel late at night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cardboard sculpture (followup)</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/27/cardboard-sculpture-followup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/27/cardboard-sculpture-followup/</guid>
      <description>Talked about this earlier. Managed to take some more pictures today and actually load them onto my computer (as opposed to deleting them accidently again. In addition to Optimus Prime, there were several milk carton people (only took a picture of one, but may go back for more later), a giant fork (didn&amp;rsquo;t take a picture because I wasn&amp;rsquo;t as enthralled by it, and it looked like it was slightly broken), a burning foosball player, and a really bizarre one involving a giant beetle pushing a dirt clod with a human fetus inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cardboard sculpture</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/25/cardboard-sculpture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/25/cardboard-sculpture/</guid>
      <description>So there&amp;rsquo;s this art class on campus that does fairly large sculptures out of cardboard. At the end of the semester, the students showcase their work out on the quad and apparently other places on campus. Saw the coolest (read: geekiest) one today in the main atrium/lobby in Beckman&amp;hellip; a 10 foot tall Optimus Prime!!! That thing rules! I&amp;rsquo;m gonna have to try to remember to bring a camera with me tomorrow to document it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OBO at it again: 9mm raffle</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/14/obo-at-it-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/14/obo-at-it-again/</guid>
      <description>Looks like the Orange and Blue Observer (OBO) are at it again. When I went to drop off my Rentertainment DVDs today, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but notice the sidewalk chalk ads everywhere for a 9mm raffle being held today on the Quad. Guess their AK-47 raffle went well enough that they decided to make some more money (and presumably make some sort of statement at the same time).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AK-47 raffle?</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/03/30/ak-47-raffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/03/30/ak-47-raffle/</guid>
      <description>Was accosted by a guy on the quad yesterday about the strangest fundraiser I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen on a college campus. This guy was selling raffle tickets to win an AK-47&amp;hellip; presumably a functional one. Didn&amp;rsquo;t probe to see if he was raising money for some &amp;ldquo;cause&amp;rdquo; or if he just had it lying around and wanted more beer money. Weird!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disgruntled Clown</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/20/disgruntled-clown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/20/disgruntled-clown/</guid>
      <description>So last weekend (not yesterday but a week before that) Amanda and I went to Bloomington to meet up with a couple of her friends from work to go see a comedy show. It was held in a dive bar (didn&amp;rsquo;t seem all that bad by campus bar standards, but it definitely wasn&amp;rsquo;t a ritzy comedy club either), and featured the Disgruntled Clown. He&amp;rsquo;s the &amp;ldquo;ex-ex-stepfather&amp;rdquo; of one of Amanda&amp;rsquo;s friends (we&amp;rsquo;re not quite sure what&amp;rsquo;s meant by the ex-ex- part&amp;hellip; not the last ex-stepfather, but the one before that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How-To-Do Girls</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/21/how-to-do-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/21/how-to-do-girls/</guid>
      <description>Ok. Ran across this weird site this morning when I was perusing suprnova. The link is howtodogirls.com. Yeah, I know what you&amp;rsquo;re thinking. Some sort of perverse instructional site. Well, you&amp;rsquo;d be right, but it&amp;rsquo;s probably not exactly what you&amp;rsquo;ve got in mind. Apparently, they&amp;rsquo;ve got a few bikini models who will do a variety of instructional videos (the episode that&amp;rsquo;s currently available is titled &amp;ldquo;Intro to Bikini Calculus&amp;rdquo;). So it&amp;rsquo;s really more of a bunch of girls doing &amp;ldquo;how-to (do)&amp;rdquo; videos instead of &amp;ldquo;how-to-do-girls&amp;rdquo; videos&amp;hellip; Weird.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fireball</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/20/fireball/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/20/fireball/</guid>
      <description>So. Was driving along last week and heard a big pow from under the hood. Knew that couldn&amp;rsquo;t be good, and it continued to make awful sounds, so I immediately pulled over and called for a tow. Tow was pretty uneventful. Just a quick hop across town via the interstate. Went in to take care of the paperwork while the driver unloaded my car. Came back out to find the car still jacked up and with the hood popped up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Jane Story: Tupperware</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/08/14/a_jane_story_tupperware/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/08/14/a_jane_story_tupperware/</guid>
      <description>So State Farm, or at least the actuarial department, has a policy that co-workers do not bring in food to help you celebrate your birthday (or any other celebration-worthy event). That would be dumb since you end up having to bring in food frequently in a large department. State Farm&amp;rsquo;s solution: the person celebrating is expected to bring in food for the department in order to celebrate. That way, you only need to bring in food once a year (ie your own birthday).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Jane Story: Jane vs. UPS</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/08/07/a_jane_story_jane_vs_ups/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/08/07/a_jane_story_jane_vs_ups/</guid>
      <description>Well, since I&amp;rsquo;ve introduced Amanda&amp;rsquo;s co-worker Jane, I suppose I should actually start posting some of the more absurd stories about her. The first one that comes to mind I will entitle &amp;ldquo;Jane vs. UPS.&amp;rdquo;
One day, Jane got it into her head to send a marinated steak to a priest friend of hers in New Jersey. So she packaged up this piece of raw, marinated steak in a bowl surrounded by ice, and put this bowl in a box and taped it shut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tales of the Weird</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/08/04/tales_of_the_weird/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/08/04/tales_of_the_weird/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to add a new category. I think I&amp;rsquo;ll title it &amp;ldquo;Tales of the Weird&amp;rdquo;, but for some reason I suspect simply &amp;ldquo;Jane Stories&amp;rdquo; would be more accurate. As such, I&amp;rsquo;ll start this category off with a brief introduction to Jane.
For those not in the know, Jane is one of Amanda&amp;rsquo;s co-workers over at State Farm corporate in Bloomington. Anyway, Jane is a weird little critter that should have been fired long ago, but somehow due to the ineptitude present in corporate America, continues to be paid to occupy space.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
