<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>huntsville on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/huntsville/</link>
    <description>Recent content in huntsville on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/huntsville/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alabama faux-snow</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/01/07/alabama-faux-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/01/07/alabama-faux-snow/</guid>
      <description>As a followup to my snow photos from Champaign at Christmas, here&amp;rsquo;s a sample of a few photos documenting what it takes to shutdown much of Huntsville:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space &amp; Rocket Center</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/23/space-rocket-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/23/space-rocket-center/</guid>
      <description>Finally caught up with going through my photos and uploading to Flickr. Katie was in town visiting this past week (Spring Break). Aside from the holy week activities (choir tired now), one afternoon Amanda and I took off work and all three of us went to the Space &amp;amp; Rocket Center. Lots of interesting historical NASA stuff (early V-2 rockets, Saturn V/Apollo stuff, etc), but I have to admit some of it felt a bit slapped together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More photos from Alabama: Cathedral Caverns, Autumn at Monte Sano, and pumpkins</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/12/16/more-photos-from-alabama-cathedral-caverns-autumn-at-monte-sano-and-pumpkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/12/16/more-photos-from-alabama-cathedral-caverns-autumn-at-monte-sano-and-pumpkins/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m finally getting around to sifting through some of the photos I&amp;rsquo;ve taken over the past couple of months and uploading them to Flickr. Here&amp;rsquo;s the one from the first batch taken at Cathedral Caverns in Scottsboro, AL:

And here are some shots I took of the Autumn trees from up on Monte Sano:

And a few shots of our pumpkins from Halloween:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As you may have noticed...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/25/as-you-may-have-noticed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/25/as-you-may-have-noticed/</guid>
      <description>Amanda and I are buying a new house. In a land far far from CU&amp;hellip; Huntsville, AL to be exact&amp;hellip; or technically Madison, AL to be even more exact (suburb to the west of Huntsville).
No, Derek didn&amp;rsquo;t graduate. While one could ask &amp;ldquo;why is he leaving sans-degree&amp;rdquo;, a better question might be &amp;ldquo;why is he referring to himself in the third person?&amp;rdquo; To put it simply, I just got fed up with how things have been going (or not going to be more precise) and decided it was time for a change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huntsville and such</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/05/10/huntsville-and-such/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/05/10/huntsville-and-such/</guid>
      <description>Those of you who know me should know why I haven&amp;rsquo;t updated in a long time. Amanda and I had a very long month when we went down to Huntsville for Mike&amp;rsquo;s wedding. We had our baby Isaac prematurely, and after fighting for three long weeks in the Huntsville NICU, he passed away peacefully in our arms. We&amp;rsquo;re still having a hard time with it, but I suppose it&amp;rsquo;s good to talk about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
