<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cats on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/cats/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cats on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/cats/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cat Diary, Day 38,974 - Now where did I leave my dignity?</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/04/24/cat-diary-day-38974-now-where-did-i-leave-my-dignity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/04/24/cat-diary-day-38974-now-where-did-i-leave-my-dignity/</guid>
      <description>My masters have hauled me down to this strange new land they keep referring to as The South. It seems like I&amp;rsquo;ve been hear for ages, which is apparently just long enough for them to inflict me with a bladder infection. I felt so uncomfortable I showed them who&amp;rsquo;s boss by peeing in things to anger them, and figured they&amp;rsquo;d break them any moment. Since they hadn&amp;rsquo;t made me better, I figured I had to be more blunt with these simpletons and started going to the litter box every fifteen minutes and I even stooped so low as to drag my ass on the carpet like a filthy dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Engineer&#39;s Guide to Cats</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/04/15/an-engineers-guide-to-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/04/15/an-engineers-guide-to-cats/</guid>
      <description>An Engineer&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Cats</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>garfield minus garfield</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/15/garfield-minus-garfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/15/garfield-minus-garfield/</guid>
      <description>Ran across this site recently, and I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I could describe it any better than the site itself does:
 Who would have guessed that when you remove Garfield from the Garfield comic strips, the result is an even better comic about schizophrenia, bipolar disorder, and the empty desperation of modern life? Friends, meet Jon Arbuckle. Let’s laugh and learn with him on a journey deep into the tortured mind of an isolated young everyman as he fights a losing battle against loneliness in a quiet American suburb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Diary, can&#39;t stand the pressure</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/22/cat-diary-cant-stand-the-pressure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/22/cat-diary-cant-stand-the-pressure/</guid>
      <description>They give me a little taste, and then take it away. I can&amp;rsquo;t take this kind of abuse. I just need my tasty kibbles. Aaah! Can&amp;rsquo;t they hear me begging for one more hit?
Tried to work out some of my energy leaping at the fun string that makes the light come on. Can you believe they left the lid to the washer open? They&amp;rsquo;re out to get me. I just can&amp;rsquo;t stand the pressure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Diary, caught sleeping</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/15/cat-diary-caught-sleeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/15/cat-diary-caught-sleeping/</guid>
      <description>Boss kitty caught me sleeping again. Don&amp;rsquo;t know why he makes such a big deal about it. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t everyone sleep like their dead?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Diary, Day 746</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/09/cat-diary-day-183/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/09/cat-diary-day-183/</guid>
      <description>Day 746 of my captivity. My captors continued to taunt me with bizarre little dangling objects. They dine lavishly on fresh meat, while I am forced to eat dry cereal.
The only thing that keeps me going is the hope of escape, and the mild satisfaction I get from clawing the furniture. Tomorrow I may eat another house plant.
Today my attempt to kill my captors by weaving around their feet while they were walking almost succeeded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some more Sammy and Spooky pics</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/08/img_1953jpg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/08/img_1953jpg/</guid>
      <description>IMG_1953.JPG
Originally uploaded by derekgottlieb.
Uploaded some new kitty pictures to flickr. Some cute pics of Sammy lounging in the laundry hamper and Spooky lounging on our bed. Spooky&amp;rsquo;s getting so big!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitty part trois</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/02/22/kitty-part-trois/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/02/22/kitty-part-trois/</guid>
      <description>We adopted our third kitty this past Saturday thanks to Amanda&amp;rsquo;s sister Katie. She&amp;rsquo;d found him as a stray hanging around the house of some of her boyfriend&amp;rsquo;s friends down in Carbondale. Seems there&amp;rsquo;s a BIG stray cat problem down in that neck of the woods (presumably because of all the college students in the area, and their decision to ditch their cats when they move). I think the call she made to Amanda about the kitty went something like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitty soup!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/30/kitty-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/30/kitty-soup/</guid>
      <description>I got some more of the disposable cameras from the wedding processed. Nothing too interesting aside from a few shots of the cats I took to use up film that I&amp;rsquo;ve put up in the usual place. Here are a couple of highlights:

Merry likes to play in the laundry
Spooky likes to play in the big soup pot Silly kitties! And now that my folks have come to visit the grand-kitties (don&amp;rsquo;t ask&amp;hellip; I didn&amp;rsquo;t coin the phrase), they have all sorts of new cat toys to play with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best blog ever!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/12/best-blog-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/12/best-blog-ever/</guid>
      <description>Ran across the best blog ever this afternoon. The Daily Kitten! Go there. NOW!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Older kitty pics</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/26/older-kitty-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/26/older-kitty-pics/</guid>
      <description>Finally got around to loading up some of my older kitty pics that were on my other camera. They start off with Spooky attacking Space Chicken when he was a little bitty kitten, and moves on to the cats playing with each other and a box.

On a related note, I did take my camera in to work today, and I did take pictures of the cardboard sculptures in Beckman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry&#39;s trip to the vet (aka a little snip-snip)</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/08/merrys-trip-to-the-vet-aka-a-little-snip-snip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/08/merrys-trip-to-the-vet-aka-a-little-snip-snip/</guid>
      <description>Dropped Merry off at the vet this morning for spaying (finally). Leaving her there all alone (overnight no less) really pulled at my heartstrings. :( I&amp;rsquo;m such a softie. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how parents manage to drop their kids off at school for the first time.
On a related note, I finally got around to uploading some more kitty pictures. Been having hardware problems with my CompactFlash reader (took forever to get it to mount, took forever to get a directory listing, took forever to transfer the files, and some of the files were corrupted by the time they got to my computer).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silly kitties!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/02/15/silly-kitties/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/02/15/silly-kitties/</guid>
      <description>Our kitties are silly! Apparently, one of our fuzzy blankets reminds Spooky an awful lot of his mama, because he&amp;rsquo;s taken to kneading, suckling, and lapping on it. I was petting him this morning (in an attempt to keep him from completely waking me up) when he started in on the blanket. He had to be going at that thing for at least half an hour. Silly kitty.
Even worse&amp;hellip; Miss Merry was getting a little old when we adopted her, but I thought vaccinations should be top priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthy Kitties!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/21/healthy-kitties/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/21/healthy-kitties/</guid>
      <description>Took Spooky into the vet today (now that his course of antibiotics is completed), and he is a healthy little kitty. Both kitties have now had their vaccinations: Merry has had the full set of rabies and FVRCP shots, and Spooky had his first dose of the FVRCP today. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to take him back in another month for the FVRCP booster, and then a month or two after that for rabies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitty part deux</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/11/kitty-part-deux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/11/kitty-part-deux/</guid>
      <description>We adopted our second kitty this past Sunday. He is an adorable 8-week old black and white kitten. He&amp;rsquo;s predominantly black with a little white stripe down his nose, a white chin and tummy, and white paws. As per the suggestion of his previous home (one of Amanda&amp;rsquo;s co-workers), we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to call him Spooky. I kept thinking of the X-Files (Fox &amp;ldquo;Spooky&amp;rdquo; Mulder), and he seems to spook pretty easily for a kitty as curious and fearless as he appears to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/28/christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/28/christmas/</guid>
      <description>Had a good Christmas this year. My folks came up the Tuesday before XMas and stayed at the new house till they left this past Sunday (ie Amanda and I ran out and bought a 2nd bed the weekend before they got here). Had a pretty good visit with them and got a chance to get my Dad&amp;rsquo;s input on some household projects.
We opened our presents to each other (Amanda, my folks, and myself) Christmas Eve&amp;hellip; my folks and Amanda liked the panoramic photos I got from LaPayne Photography (thanks Rachel!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitties!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/02/kitties/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/02/kitties/</guid>
      <description>So slashdot had an interesting IT review link today: Juvenile felis catus (or &amp;ldquo;kitten&amp;rdquo; for you laymen). Full of very cute pictures, a lot of tongue-in-cheek commentary, and links to all sorts of amusing/geeky/just plain weird sites (standard kitten package and CAT Users&#39; Manual). Oh, and he even provides a convenient summary comparison against competing models (i.e. puppies, babies, or a new video card). Now that Amanda and I have a house, we&amp;rsquo;ll get to start looking for kittens before long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cutest Kitten</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/06/10/cutest_kitten/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/06/10/cutest_kitten/</guid>
      <description>This has got to be the cutest kitten ever! So sleepy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
