<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>music on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/categories/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in music on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/categories/music/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Evanescence: DI Photo</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/10/evanescence_di_photo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/10/evanescence_di_photo/</guid>
      <description>Looks like the DI did actually send a photographer to the Evanescence concert&amp;hellip; they just never bothered to publish a story or any photos about it until now. Basically, they&amp;rsquo;ve got a feature on the DI Finest Photos of 2004 (little presumptuous seeing as the year&amp;rsquo;s not even half over). But apparently, they thought this photo of Evanescence was one of their best of the year. Why it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have warranted publishing earlier on that basis, I don&amp;rsquo;t know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Folds followup</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/07/ben_folds_followup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/07/ben_folds_followup/</guid>
      <description>So Richy had some nice news for me. Turns out somebody managed to get a high quality bootleg of Monday&amp;rsquo;s concert up by Tuesday afternoon. Quality&amp;rsquo;s quite good, so you may want to check it out. Also, Richy&amp;rsquo;s got his pictures up from the concert now. You can see them here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Folds</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/06/ben_folds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/06/ben_folds/</guid>
      <description>So Amanda and I (along with Richy, Carrie, Lee, and Dan) went to the Ben Folds concert last night at Foellinger. The show was great! The opening act was a great string trio led by David Berkeley on guitar, and assisted by Will Robertson on upright bass and Adam Buchwald(?) on mandolin. They were really good. I loved the mix of the 3 instruments. You should definitely check out David Berkeley if you get the chance (there&amp;rsquo;s a mp3 available for download on his page of a song &amp;ldquo;Fire Sign&amp;rdquo; that was featured in CBS&#39; show Without a Trace).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evanescence</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/02/26/evanescence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/02/26/evanescence/</guid>
      <description>So I saw Evanescence in concert this past Tuesday at the Assembly Hall. Great show.
First opening act, Atomship, was kinda eh. They weren&amp;rsquo;t awful, but they certainly weren&amp;rsquo;t very good either. Lead singer was pretty weird. Had something vaguely resembling a British accent until he mentioned they were from Mississippi when he suddenly reverted to a good ol&#39; boy accent. And he had this weird twitchy, seizurey sort of &amp;ldquo;dance&amp;rdquo; thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liz Phair followup</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/12/02/liz_phair_followup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/12/02/liz_phair_followup/</guid>
      <description>Just wanted to post a quick followup to my previous Liz Phair post. Found this pretty cool shot of her performing at Foellinger (courtesy of the Daily Illini).
I lost count, but I believe she rotated between 3 Fender electrics and some sort of acoustic during the course of the show with her roadie retuning between swaps. She claimed she had to swap out guitars a lot because he would have to retune depending on the song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liz Phair</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/11/18/liz_phair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/11/18/liz_phair/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, so things have been pretty busy the past several months, and I haven&amp;rsquo;t made any posts here since the fall semester started. Anyway, just wanted to pop on here to say I went to the Liz Phair concert last night and it rocked. Quite outstanding. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard her stuff, and like &amp;ldquo;chick rock&amp;rdquo;, I&amp;rsquo;d suggest checking her out. Her most recent album is more pop than her older stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
