<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ireland on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/ireland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ireland on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/ireland/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Photo usage</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/30/photo-usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/30/photo-usage/</guid>
      <description>Apparently it&amp;rsquo;s been a busy week for my flickr photos. I&amp;rsquo;ve had two that were selected for inclusion in various web things.
First, one of my Ireland honeymoon photos was selected for inclusion in Schmap Dublin Third Edition (check out Literary Dublin: Trinity College). Oddly enough, it was a photo I took while we were wandering around Trinity College. Here&amp;rsquo;s a little descriptive blurb from their website:
 Exploring a Schmap Guide is a uniquely interactive experience: maps and guide content are dynamically integrated, allowing intuitive, real-time access to reviews and photo slideshows for places of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ireland Photos</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/01/ireland_photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/01/ireland_photos/</guid>
      <description>I think I&amp;rsquo;ve got the bulk of the photos from our honeymoon in Ireland cleaned up and uploaded. You should be able to view them now here. I tried setting it up to auto-resize them when I uploaded (since I don&amp;rsquo;t have the disk space to store them all full res), but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I want them any bigger than it&amp;rsquo;s currently set to. If you&amp;rsquo;ve got any feedback in that respect, please let me know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re back!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/06/30/were_back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/06/30/were_back/</guid>
      <description>So Amanda and I got back from our honeymoon in Ireland Monday night. We pretty much up and died when we got home. Very long day. Spent yesterday trying to get shifted back by 6 hours and deal with essential errands. We&amp;rsquo;ve had all of Amanda&amp;rsquo;s film developed onto CD, and I offloaded all of my digital pics to my computer. The photos are largely sorted by this point, but need some cleanup before I&amp;rsquo;ll put them up on the web.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
