<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>btrfs on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/btrfs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in btrfs on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/btrfs/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Btrfs production experiences</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2013/04/29/btrfs-production-experiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2013/04/29/btrfs-production-experiences/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My experience is based on SUSE SLES 11 SP1/SP2 with a stock kernel, so YMMV if
you&amp;rsquo;re running a newer mainline kernel without all the backports.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tested on two Supermicro systems. One with an LSI HBA card with 22x 2TB
enterprise SATA drives (originally purchased to run OpenSolaris/ZFS). Second
has an Adaptec hardware RAID controller with 36x 2TB enterprise SATA drives.
Some of the data loss and stability issues I experienced may be attributed to
later discovering the &amp;ldquo;enterprise&amp;rdquo; drives used in the first system turned out
to be less RAID-friendly than the manufacturer claimed, eventually leading to
them to replace ALL of my drives with a different model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Btrfs was a preview in SLES SP1 and is &amp;ldquo;supported&amp;rdquo; in SP2 but with major
restrictions if you wanted a supported configuration. Support in SP2 requires
that you create btrfs filesystems using Yast and live with the limited options
it allows.  I&amp;rsquo;m guessing what you can do via Yast is the subset of features
they tested enough to be willing to try and support.  I tried using Yast to set
up btrfs on one of our systems, but found their constraints too limiting given
my use case and the organization I&amp;rsquo;d settled on in the SP1 days.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
