<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>film on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/film/</link>
    <description>Recent content in film on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 08:22:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/film/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Weeklyish musings: 2023-01-07</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2023/01/07/weeklyish-musings-2023-01-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 08:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2023/01/07/weeklyish-musings-2023-01-07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-im-reading&#34;&gt;What I&amp;rsquo;m reading&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Hero of Ages&amp;rdquo;, Brandon Sanderson (audiobook).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Mapping the Interior&amp;rdquo;, Stephen Graham Jones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Winterborne Home for Mayhem and Mystery&amp;rdquo;, Ally Carter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Better off Dead&amp;rdquo;, Lee Child and Andrew Child.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Ghost Brigades&amp;rdquo;, John Scalzi (audiobook).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-im-watching&#34;&gt;What I&amp;rsquo;m watching&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt6710474&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Everything Everywhere All at Once&amp;rdquo; (2022)&lt;/a&gt; :mindblown:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt1798709&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;her&amp;rdquo; (2013)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-im-playing&#34;&gt;What I&amp;rsquo;m playing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://bethesda.net/game/deathloop&#34;&gt;Deathloop&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Buff meme</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/25/movie-buff-meme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/25/movie-buff-meme/</guid>
      <description>Your Movie Buff Quotient: 88%
You are a movie buff of the most obsessive variety. If a movie exists, chances are that you&amp;rsquo;ve seen it.
You&amp;rsquo;re an expert on movie facts and trivia. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to stump you with a question about film.
Are You a Movie Buff?
Response from anyone who knows me:
well, duh. of course you&amp;rsquo;re a movie geek.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joost coolness</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/09/joost-coolness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/09/joost-coolness/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how to describe Joost aside from on-demand, internet tv clips from the crew that put together Skype and Kazaa. A while back I managed to land an invite from Joost for their private beta test, and have enjoyed running it on my Macbook Pro (they support Windows and Intel Macs at this point). Very little lag when you first fire up a program, and haven&amp;rsquo;t had any issues once a show starts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simpsons Movie... and create your own avatar!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/07/simpsons-movie-and-create-your-own-avatar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/07/simpsons-movie-and-create-your-own-avatar/</guid>
      <description>So the Simpsons are headed for movie theaters everywhere toward the end of the month. Supposedly it&amp;rsquo;s good, but I think I&amp;rsquo;ll wait for the rental. What prompts me to write this post however is one of the features available on the movie website&amp;hellip; create your own Simpsons avatar! Reasonably well done Flash affair where you select body type, hairstyle, eyebrows, eyes, nose, mouth, etc. There&amp;rsquo;s of course only a limited number of each of these, but you can achieve a fairly reasonable likeness and save it out as a jpeg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies, Music, and Birthdays Oh My!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/11/28/movies-music-and-birthdays-oh-my/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/11/28/movies-music-and-birthdays-oh-my/</guid>
      <description>Took a vacation of sorts down to SoFlo (hey, SoCal&amp;rsquo;s accepted, why not SoFlo for the sunshine state?) with Amanda to visit the folk this past week for Thanksgiving and Birthdays and so forth. Really spent a fair portion of my time going through the crap in my room from my childhood. Not so fun and I&amp;rsquo;m surprised Amanda didn&amp;rsquo;t kill me for wasting her limited vacation time in this manner, but at least we got to go to Monkey Jungle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aeon Flux the movie???</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/08/24/aeon-flux-the-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/08/24/aeon-flux-the-movie/</guid>
      <description>Holy crap! There&amp;rsquo;s an Aeon Flux movie in the works! Live action no less! Used to watch this way back in the day on MTV&amp;rsquo;s Liquid Television in the middle of the night&amp;hellip; Wild, bizarre, risque stuff.
Be sure to go check out the trailer. I really don&amp;rsquo;t remember the show having quite that much plot. :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies DB themed</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/06/27/movies-themed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/06/27/movies-themed/</guid>
      <description>Finally got around to integrating my movies page with the rest of the site. It&amp;rsquo;s definitely hacky at this point (made a custom wordpress page style containing most of the php code and simply created an empty page that uses that style), but at least it works. Still need to refine it some. I stripped out most of the db fields from getting displayed since I&amp;rsquo;m don&amp;rsquo;t have as much screen width to work with, but I should fine tune what I display.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh happy days!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/06/27/oh-happy-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/06/27/oh-happy-days/</guid>
      <description>Just decided to go poking around the web to see if there was any news about a DVD release of Kenneth Branaugh&amp;rsquo;s Hamlet. Turns out there is! Warner Home Video is slated to release a 10th anniversary special edition DVD in 2006! Kick-ass!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revenge of the Sith</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/19/revenge-of-the-sith/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/19/revenge-of-the-sith/</guid>
      <description>Star Wars: Episode III is out! And it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to be good. Very dark, but good. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard it actually does a good job wrapping things up and bridging the new with the old. Hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll get to see it before too long (headed out of town to go to Amanda&amp;rsquo;s cousin&amp;rsquo;s wedding tomorrow and my folks will be here next week). Of course, I&amp;rsquo;ve heard a fairly high quality work print has been leaked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serenity Trailer!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/26/serenity-trailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/26/serenity-trailer/</guid>
      <description>Looks like the trailer for Joss Whedon&amp;rsquo;s Serenity (based on the series Firefly) is finally online! Looks pretty tight. How am I gonna make it till September 30th when it&amp;rsquo;s finally released? Makes me want to go back and rewatch the show again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV I&#39;ve missed</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/03/31/tv-ive-missed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/03/31/tv-ive-missed/</guid>
      <description>TV on DVD is so very cool. After a recommendation from Lee (not to mention my own curiosity), I rented the first disc of Joss Whedon&amp;rsquo;s Firefly a few weeks back. Really enjoyed it, so I ended up buying it. Good stuff.
Sticking with the trend, I decided to go rent the first couple of discs for BBC&amp;rsquo;s MI-5. It had piqued my interest previously, but hadn&amp;rsquo;t gotten around to looking for it until the recent issue of Wired reminded me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raiders</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/30/raiders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/30/raiders/</guid>
      <description>Went to the Castle Theater in Bloomington yesterday with Amanda to see Raiders of the Lost Ark. Really outstanding theater setup. Instead of the usual uncomfortable, cramped stadium seating, the Castle has a set of squishy couches and loveseats. Much more enjoyable experience. Raiders is such a classic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grudge</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/18/the-grudge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/18/the-grudge/</guid>
      <description>Just saw a trailer for The Grudge with SMG. Looks excellently creepy! Man. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna have to go see that. Makes me want to go watch The Ring, another creepy Japanese movie remake (haven&amp;rsquo;t actually gotten around to seeing it yet, just heard about it).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alias: Season 3</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/09/06/alias-season-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/09/06/alias-season-3/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t wait! Season 3 of Alias will be released on DVD tomorrow. Think I&amp;rsquo;ll break down and pick up the first two seasons while I&amp;rsquo;m at it (only borrowed them from Richy previously). Probably need to go back and re-watch a bit of Season 2 to remember where things left off. Unfortunately, Season 4 won&amp;rsquo;t start until January. :(</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebToons: Angry Alien</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/19/webtoons_angry_alien/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/19/webtoons_angry_alien/</guid>
      <description>Angry Alien has a series of WebToons that are popular movies in 30 seconds&amp;hellip; re-enacted by bunnies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebToons: Happy Tree Friends</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/19/webtoons_happy_tree_friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/19/webtoons_happy_tree_friends/</guid>
      <description>Who can forget the Happy Tree Friends when they&amp;rsquo;re talking about bizarre little WebToons? The series consists of a bunch of shorts of little cute fuzzy animals meeting their demise in a disturbing manner. Fun for the whole family. I also ran across this site that appeared to have all of the episodes available for convenient viewing (I don&amp;rsquo;t think the official site has all of the older ones). These toons have even come out on DVD if you can believe it (that&amp;rsquo;s how I first saw them).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Screensavers</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/06/the_screensavers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/06/the_screensavers/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty religiously watching The Screensavers on G4/TechTV since I noticed the cable company added it to the lineup. Pretty entertaining show, and they sometimes have some cool bits on there. This past week they had a Best of: Free and Cheap episode detailing a number of free/cheap downloads and tips. I found a couple of segments of particular interest:
Linksys WRT54G - a lot of the Linksys network hardware runs Linux, and so they&amp;rsquo;ve had to release the source under GPL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebToons: Amy Winfrey</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/19/webtoons_amy_winfrey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/19/webtoons_amy_winfrey/</guid>
      <description>So recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching some webtoons done by Amy Winfrey (works as an animator for South Park), and they&amp;rsquo;re pretty cute. I started watching her current toon, Making Fiends, that revolves around two little girls, Vendetta and Charlotte, who go to school together. Vendetta makes all sorts of fiends and attempts to intimidate and destroy Charlotte, while Charlotte&amp;rsquo;s busy making friends. That led me to her previous set of toons, MuffinFilms, which are a variety of short animations involving muffins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#define McGuffin</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/02/define_mcguffin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/02/define_mcguffin/</guid>
      <description>McGuffin (aka: MacGuffin or maguffin) is a term for a plot enabling device, i.e. a device or plot element in a movie that is deliberately placed to catch the viewer&amp;rsquo;s attention and/or drive the logic of the plot, but which actually serves no further purpose - it won&amp;rsquo;t pop up again later, it won&amp;rsquo;t explain the ending, it won&amp;rsquo;t actually do anything except possibly distract you while you try to figure out its significance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
