<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>snow on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/snow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in snow on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/snow/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alabama faux-snow</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/01/07/alabama-faux-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/01/07/alabama-faux-snow/</guid>
      <description>As a followup to my snow photos from Champaign at Christmas, here&amp;rsquo;s a sample of a few photos documenting what it takes to shutdown much of Huntsville:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas snow in Illinois</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/01/07/christmas-snow-in-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/01/07/christmas-snow-in-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Finally getting around to going through photos I&amp;rsquo;ve taken recently and uploaded a set I took of the snow while we were in Champaign for Christmas. Here&amp;rsquo;s a sample that I liked with Sarah chasing Rachel down the street with a snow shovel full of snow:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blizzard pics &#39;07</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/15/blizzard-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/15/blizzard-pics/</guid>
      <description>Took some pictures of the snow yesterday and put them up on flickr:

We definitely got a fair bit of snow, and some of the drifts were pretty impressive. Unfortunately, the winds and the city plows concentrated and packed the snow on our side of the street (but it did mean our street was plowed a few times as opposed to the more minor streets that maybe saw one pass&amp;hellip; benefits of being a city and school bus route).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hell hath frozen over, Part III</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/14/hell-hath-frozen-over-part-iii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/14/hell-hath-frozen-over-part-iii/</guid>
      <description>Apparently the UofI hasn&amp;rsquo;t called a snow day since &amp;lsquo;79. That&amp;rsquo;s close to 30 years of no snow days. They had some silly spokesperson on the news last night that tried to claim we were such a hardy campus and liked to walk everywhere so it took an awful lot to shut us down. Apparently they decided that severe blizzard conditions with 45mph gusts and snow falling way faster than the plows could ever hope to keep up with might actually warrant a snow day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hell hath frozen over</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/13/hell-hath-frozen-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/13/hell-hath-frozen-over/</guid>
      <description>All classes have been canceled for Tuesday (Feb. 13) at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign. More than 5 inches of snow fell overnight, up to another foot of snow is possible by Tuesday night and a blizzard warning is in effect. U. of I. employees who have been designated as essential personnel are expected to report to work.
This mailing approved by: The Office of the Chancellor
 The U of I never cancels class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hell hath frozen over, Continued</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/13/hell-hath-frozen-over-continued/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/13/hell-hath-frozen-over-continued/</guid>
      <description>All Wednesday (Feb. 14) classes at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign have been cancelled.
Continuing high winds and snow have made it impossible to keep streets and sidewalks clear and safe.
Only personnel providing critical services should continue to report for each work shift until further notice. Employees uncertain about their status should direct any questions to their supervisors.
Classes at the U. of I. Child Development Lab also are cancelled for Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
