<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>travel on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in travel on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/travel/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nashville Photos: Lane Motor Museum</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/05/03/nashville-photos-lane-motor-museum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/05/03/nashville-photos-lane-motor-museum/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago, we went up to Nashville and hit a number of the sights. I&amp;rsquo;ll go ahead and split this into two posts, since I&amp;rsquo;ve only uploaded some of the relevant photos so far. The first day, we hit their recreation of the Parthenon. Apparently, it&amp;rsquo;s actually the second replica they&amp;rsquo;ve built, with the first being built in 1897 to celebrate their centennial but it was only built to last 6 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More photos from Savannah trip: Museum of Aviation</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/23/more-photos-from-savannah-trip-museum-of-aviation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/23/more-photos-from-savannah-trip-museum-of-aviation/</guid>
      <description>On the drive back from Savannah, Charles and I quickly stopped in to visit the Robins Air Force Base Museum of Aviation. Didn&amp;rsquo;t spend very long there, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t too much out of the way for the drive back and had a chance to take a few pics. There were some more unusual planes there that I&amp;rsquo;d meant to go back and look up info on, but obviously hadn&amp;rsquo;t since I only just pulled the photos off my camera a few days ago with the rest of the photos from Savannah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Savannah</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/19/savannah/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/19/savannah/</guid>
      <description>Took a trip for work back in December to provide cluster training for some of the engineers at Gulfstream. Seems like we also did some very minor maintenance on the cluster we administer there. Anyway, I brought the camera along and had a chance to take a few pics while wandering around the riverfront. Only got around to pulling them off my camera today, so here they are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo usage</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/30/photo-usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/30/photo-usage/</guid>
      <description>Apparently it&amp;rsquo;s been a busy week for my flickr photos. I&amp;rsquo;ve had two that were selected for inclusion in various web things.
First, one of my Ireland honeymoon photos was selected for inclusion in Schmap Dublin Third Edition (check out Literary Dublin: Trinity College). Oddly enough, it was a photo I took while we were wandering around Trinity College. Here&amp;rsquo;s a little descriptive blurb from their website:
Exploring a Schmap Guide is a uniquely interactive experience: maps and guide content are dynamically integrated, allowing intuitive, real-time access to reviews and photo slideshows for places of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Fran and Pumpkins</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/10/30/san-fran-and-pumpkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/10/30/san-fran-and-pumpkins/</guid>
      <description>Have some pics up from my trip to the bay area up at Flickr:
Was a good trip overall. Real good to see Richy and Carrie and get to hang out with them some and see some sights. Got up to the Golden Gate bridge, although didn&amp;rsquo;t see that much since it was really foggy. Headed down to the Fisherman&amp;rsquo;s Wharf and wandered around there for a while checking out the sea lions and Ghirardelli and such.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies, Music, and Birthdays Oh My!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/11/28/movies-music-and-birthdays-oh-my/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/11/28/movies-music-and-birthdays-oh-my/</guid>
      <description>Took a vacation of sorts down to SoFlo (hey, SoCal&amp;rsquo;s accepted, why not SoFlo for the sunshine state?) with Amanda to visit the folk this past week for Thanksgiving and Birthdays and so forth. Really spent a fair portion of my time going through the crap in my room from my childhood. Not so fun and I&amp;rsquo;m surprised Amanda didn&amp;rsquo;t kill me for wasting her limited vacation time in this manner, but at least we got to go to Monkey Jungle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago photos</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/13/chicago-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/13/chicago-photos/</guid>
      <description>Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve uploaded bits and pieces of the Chicago photos (still not quite done sifting through the stuff from the Field Museum or any of my skyline/downtown shots or those in Millenium Park). You can check them out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Museum Goodness</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/12/chicago-museum-goodness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/12/chicago-museum-goodness/</guid>
      <description>Amanda and I just got back last night from a long weekend trip up to Chicago. Headed up there Friday morning and hit the Shedd Aquarium, apparently oldest aquarium in the country (founded 75 years ago). Since we were planning on hitting lots of museums, we picked up &amp;ldquo;city passes&amp;rdquo; that include admission to a number of different sites in the area (if you see more than two of the six, I think you made out well).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding, wedding, and more weddings...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/30/weddings-wedding-and-more-weddings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/30/weddings-wedding-and-more-weddings/</guid>
      <description>Been rather busy lately. Went to my cousin&amp;rsquo;s wedding 3 weekends ago in Missouri/Kansas. Then flew down to Amanda&amp;rsquo;s cousin&amp;rsquo;s wedding in Texas 2 weekends ago. My folks have been visiting this past week and just left on Sunday morning. To top that off, I&amp;rsquo;ve had some sort of nasty sinus infection for the past week. Next weekend we&amp;rsquo;re off to Iowa for Amanda&amp;rsquo;s coworker&amp;rsquo;s wedding and on the way back I&amp;rsquo;ll be going to ISCA &amp;lsquo;05 in Wisconsin for a few days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ireland Photos</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/01/ireland_photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/01/ireland_photos/</guid>
      <description>I think I&amp;rsquo;ve got the bulk of the photos from our honeymoon in Ireland cleaned up and uploaded. You should be able to view them now here. I tried setting it up to auto-resize them when I uploaded (since I don&amp;rsquo;t have the disk space to store them all full res), but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I want them any bigger than it&amp;rsquo;s currently set to. If you&amp;rsquo;ve got any feedback in that respect, please let me know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re back!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/06/30/were_back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/06/30/were_back/</guid>
      <description>So Amanda and I got back from our honeymoon in Ireland Monday night. We pretty much up and died when we got home. Very long day. Spent yesterday trying to get shifted back by 6 hours and deal with essential errands. We&amp;rsquo;ve had all of Amanda&amp;rsquo;s film developed onto CD, and I offloaded all of my digital pics to my computer. The photos are largely sorted by this point, but need some cleanup before I&amp;rsquo;ll put them up on the web.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
