<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gaming on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/gaming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gaming on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 18:52:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/gaming/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Weekly-ish (?) musings: 2022-12-09</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2022/12/09/weekly-ish-musings-2022-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 18:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2022/12/09/weekly-ish-musings-2022-12-09/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-im-reading&#34;&gt;What I&amp;rsquo;m reading&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Ghost Story&amp;rdquo;, Peter Straub (audiobook). I was hopeful after having enjoyed his collaborations with Stephen King
(&amp;ldquo;The Talisman&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Black House&amp;rdquo;). While I enjoyed some of the prose, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I would&amp;rsquo;ve made it through if I
were reading it instead of listening while doing other things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In progress:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;The End of the World: Stories of the Apocalypse&amp;rdquo;, multiple authors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Side Jobs: Stories from the Dresden Files&amp;rdquo;, Jim Butcher.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Odyssey&amp;rdquo;, Homer / Emily Wilson (translator) (audiobook).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Winterborne Home for Vengeance and Valor&amp;rdquo;, Ally Carter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-im-playing&#34;&gt;What I&amp;rsquo;m playing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1182310/The_Excavation_of_Hobs_Barrow/&#34;&gt;The Excavation of Hob&amp;rsquo;s Barrow&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1332010/Stray/&#34;&gt;Stray&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exult - open-source Ultima 7 engine</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/12/12/exult-open-source-ultima-7-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/12/12/exult-open-source-ultima-7-engine/</guid>
      <description>So recently I&amp;rsquo;d been thinking a fair bit about how good some old DOS games were back in the day. The ones that really came to mind were the Ultima series (particularly U6: The False Prophet, U7: The Black Gate, and U7: Serpent Isle). Those were outstanding games. I&amp;rsquo;d done a bit of research and found DOSBox, which allows you to play a wide range of old DOS games on an assortment of platforms (ie it performs x86/DOS emulation).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zelda delayed :(</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/09/28/zelda-delayed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/09/28/zelda-delayed/</guid>
      <description>How lame! I&amp;rsquo;ve talked about this game a little previously, and it&amp;rsquo;s looking pretty oustanding. They&amp;rsquo;ve gone back to more of a realistic look from the cel-shaded cartoony stuff of Wind Waker. Not that Wind Waker wasn&amp;rsquo;t cool. But it sounds like it&amp;rsquo;s getting pushed back from November to some time after next March or so (according to IGN). Man, this was announced back in August. Where was I? I&amp;rsquo;m really looking forward to this game too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What the... Nintendo&#39;s new controller?</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/09/16/what-the-nintendos-new-controller/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/09/16/what-the-nintendos-new-controller/</guid>
      <description>Nintendo&amp;rsquo;s finally announced the controller for their next-gen console (the Revolution). Does anyone besides me find it bizarre?
Sounds like it&amp;rsquo;s somewhere between a one-handed tv remote and an old power glove? There are apparently a couple of sensors placed near the tv plus a sensor in the remote that detect position and orientation. They plan on supporting other &amp;ldquo;more traditional&amp;rdquo; controller types (conventional controller shells, dance mats, bongos, etc) by slipping the remote inside these other add-ons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E3 Highlights</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/19/e3-highlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/19/e3-highlights/</guid>
      <description>The big E3 entertainment expo featured the first real info on the next generation game consoles. Xbox360 features a PowerPC with 3 cores, graphics by ATI, some backwards compatibility. PS3 features a beastly PowerPC-based Cell processor (ie roughly twice the flops of the Xbox360), graphics by Nvidia, Blu-Ray support, and full backwards compatibility (PS1 and PS2). Very limited details on the Nintendo Revolution: backwards compatible with Gamecube games, support for downloading old school Nintendo games (NES, SNES, N64&amp;hellip; not sure how the pricing scheme will work for this).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zelda trailers</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/03/15/zelda-trailers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/03/15/zelda-trailers/</guid>
      <description>Just tell me this doesn&amp;rsquo;t look totally awesome!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEGO Star Wars</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/14/lego-star-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/14/lego-star-wars/</guid>
      <description>So Lego&amp;rsquo;s working on a video game set in the Lego Star Wars universe (ie Star Wars setting, but stuff is built out of Legos). They have some coverage over at Gamespot, including screenshots. Looks like it should be a pretty cute game, and the initial hands-on demo is impressive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/09/27/the-kingdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/09/27/the-kingdom/</guid>
      <description>So what&amp;rsquo;ve I been up to recently&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ve been adventuring in the Kingdom&amp;hellip; The Kingom of Loathing that is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duct Tape</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/07/duct_tape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/07/duct_tape/</guid>
      <description>Looks like someone heard me. There&amp;rsquo;s now a mod out there for Doom 3 that attaches a small flashlight to the shotgun and machinegun. Claims to be using Duct Tape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MoH: Pacific Assault</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/07/moh_pacific_assault/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/07/moh_pacific_assault/</guid>
      <description>Looks like EA has pushed back the release of Medal of Honor: Pacific Assault to some time in November. Guess they&amp;rsquo;re adding some form of squad control (basic orders like advance, fall back, suppressive fire, etc) and some general polishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doom!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/06/doom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/06/doom/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing Doom 3 off and on most of this week. If you like the Doom series, this is a welcome refresher. The graphics are pretty tight (although I don&amp;rsquo;t actually have a machine set up that&amp;rsquo;s fast enough to really crank it up beyond the lowest possible settings&amp;hellip; I do have most of the effects like bump mapping and stuff turned on though). Gameplay is pretty much what you&amp;rsquo;d expect from a Doom game, but I kinda like the combo of the dark environment and having to use a flashlight (which looks pretty damn good).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leather?</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/02/leather/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/02/leather/</guid>
      <description>Ok. So I was poking around Gamestop, and ran across this. Can you believe it? For those of you who just couldn&amp;rsquo;t get enough leather, a leather computer mouse?
Anyway, I can&amp;rsquo;t wait till Doom 3 hits shelves, hopefully tomorrow. Now I just have to wait for Half-Life 2, which looks awesome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spy Fiction</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/24/spy_fiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/24/spy_fiction/</guid>
      <description>This game looks to be pretty sweet. Another game in the stealth genre (ala Metal Gear), but the guy in this one wears a funky suit that lets him turn invisible when he crouches (somehow more believable than hiding in a little shadow). He can also emulate the appearance of any character he takes a picture of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evil Genius</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/19/evil_genius/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/19/evil_genius/</guid>
      <description>Man, I&amp;rsquo;m totally looking forward to Evil Genius for the PC. General concept reminds me of the old Dungeon Keeper series where you were an evil demon who had all sorts of minions and had to build and defend your dungeon against those darn heroes. Used to love those games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E3</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/14/e3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/14/e3/</guid>
      <description>So I dug around for a bit, and ran across some pretty thorough coverage of the games at E3 over at GameSpot. All sorts of good stuff coming up. In the FPS category, you&amp;rsquo;ve got Doom 3, Half-Life 2, Halo 2 that all look pretty good. There&amp;rsquo;s the next Grand Theft Auto (San Andreas). The next Gran Turismo looks absolutely amazing. And they&amp;rsquo;ve got a little info on the upcoming Zelda game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zelda!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/13/zelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/13/zelda/</guid>
      <description>So Nintendo&amp;rsquo;s released some screenshots and a trailer for an upcoming Zelda game. Looks freakin&amp;rsquo; awesome. I&amp;rsquo;m totally looking forward to this one!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
