<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>humor on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/humor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in humor on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/humor/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Because I&#39;m a Princess!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2015/04/27/because-im-a-princess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2015/04/27/because-im-a-princess/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://youtu.be/hHmiZ_OMMkI&#34;&gt;This pretty well sums up my younger daughter, Nora.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Odd request from someone at the Public Health Foundation</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2015/02/15/odd-request-from-someone-at-the-public-health-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2015/02/15/odd-request-from-someone-at-the-public-health-foundation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently, someone from the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.phf.org/&#34;&gt;Public Health Foundation&lt;/a&gt;
contacted me because they found a blog post I had from back in 2005,
specifically &lt;a href=&#34;https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/28/corporategovernment-parodies-on-the-web/&#34;&gt;Corporate/Government Parodies on the
Web&lt;/a&gt;. They asked if
I&amp;rsquo;d like to update the broken reference to mypyramid.gov (which no longer
exists) in favor of a new government nutrition website. Having gone back and
re-read the post for context, I initially thought I&amp;rsquo;d just ignore it for the
moment since I figured it had to be some automated webcrawler of sending emails
to DNS contacts for any hits referencing the old .gov URL. But they actually
sent me a followup email, so I thought I might go ahead and make some updates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Saint Patrick&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/03/18/happy-saint-patricks-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/03/18/happy-saint-patricks-day/</guid>
      <description>To celebrate, here&amp;rsquo;s some awesomeness from Mobile, AL:
Leprechaun in Mobile, Alabama</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Diary, Day 38,974 - Now where did I leave my dignity?</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/04/24/cat-diary-day-38974-now-where-did-i-leave-my-dignity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/04/24/cat-diary-day-38974-now-where-did-i-leave-my-dignity/</guid>
      <description>My masters have hauled me down to this strange new land they keep referring to as The South. It seems like I&amp;rsquo;ve been hear for ages, which is apparently just long enough for them to inflict me with a bladder infection. I felt so uncomfortable I showed them who&amp;rsquo;s boss by peeing in things to anger them, and figured they&amp;rsquo;d break them any moment. Since they hadn&amp;rsquo;t made me better, I figured I had to be more blunt with these simpletons and started going to the litter box every fifteen minutes and I even stooped so low as to drag my ass on the carpet like a filthy dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Engineer&#39;s Guide to Cats</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/04/15/an-engineers-guide-to-cats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/04/15/an-engineers-guide-to-cats/</guid>
      <description>An Engineer&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Cats</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>garfield minus garfield</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/15/garfield-minus-garfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/15/garfield-minus-garfield/</guid>
      <description>Ran across this site recently, and I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I could describe it any better than the site itself does:
 Who would have guessed that when you remove Garfield from the Garfield comic strips, the result is an even better comic about schizophrenia, bipolar disorder, and the empty desperation of modern life? Friends, meet Jon Arbuckle. Let’s laugh and learn with him on a journey deep into the tortured mind of an isolated young everyman as he fights a losing battle against loneliness in a quiet American suburb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas, Movie-House!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/12/25/merry-christmas-movie-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/12/25/merry-christmas-movie-house/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s that time of year. Time to watch favorites like &amp;ldquo;How the Grinch Stole Christmas&amp;rdquo; (the real one, not that live-action debacle starring Jim Carrey and directed by Ron Howard) and &amp;ldquo;A Christmas Story&amp;rdquo; (they looked at me like i had lobsters crawling out of my ears!). Seems like Christmas has rushed up to me before I had a chance to notice. Fortunately I was able to get the little bit of shopping I wanted to do done yesterday, and no it wasn&amp;rsquo;t nearly as bad as I had feared.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#define meme</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/09/define-meme-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/09/define-meme-2/</guid>
      <description>Main Entry: meme
Pronunciation: \ˈmēm\
Function: noun
Etymology: alteration of mimeme, from mim- (as in mimesis) + -eme
Date: 1976
1 : an idea, behavior, style, or usage that spreads from person to person within a culture
[Source]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Diary, can&#39;t stand the pressure</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/22/cat-diary-cant-stand-the-pressure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/22/cat-diary-cant-stand-the-pressure/</guid>
      <description>They give me a little taste, and then take it away. I can&amp;rsquo;t take this kind of abuse. I just need my tasty kibbles. Aaah! Can&amp;rsquo;t they hear me begging for one more hit?
Tried to work out some of my energy leaping at the fun string that makes the light come on. Can you believe they left the lid to the washer open? They&amp;rsquo;re out to get me. I just can&amp;rsquo;t stand the pressure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Diary, Day 752</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/15/cat-diary-day-752/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/15/cat-diary-day-752/</guid>
      <description>Day 752 of my captivity. Found what I hope is one of my captor&amp;rsquo;s favorite possessions. It appears to be some sort of container for transporting instruments of my exploitation and I believe it to be associated with their obnoxious light flashing device.
I have thoroughly inspected it&amp;rsquo;s contents to ascertain if it might hold anything I could use in my escape. Having found nothing, I destroyed it&amp;rsquo;s lining with my claws and ate the outer edges to prevent its further use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Diary, Day 746</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/09/cat-diary-day-183/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/09/cat-diary-day-183/</guid>
      <description>Day 746 of my captivity. My captors continued to taunt me with bizarre little dangling objects. They dine lavishly on fresh meat, while I am forced to eat dry cereal.
The only thing that keeps me going is the hope of escape, and the mild satisfaction I get from clawing the furniture. Tomorrow I may eat another house plant.
Today my attempt to kill my captors by weaving around their feet while they were walking almost succeeded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#define manscaping</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/02/24/define-manscaping/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/02/24/define-manscaping/</guid>
      <description>manscaping: to groom a man. Shaving, waxing, cleaning up the superfluous fur.
Courtest of the Urban Dictionary.Â A collaborative (think wikipedia) dictionary for modern slang.Â Found out about this earlier this week on the Rep yahoo group.Â Since a lot of slang is a bit crude in nature, I don&amp;rsquo;t have to warn you that this site may offend some of the prudish folk out there.Â You&amp;rsquo;ve been warned&amp;hellip;Â I could probably spend all day looking through that site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#define meme</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/09/22/define-meme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/09/22/define-meme/</guid>
      <description>Pronunciation:	&amp;lsquo;mEm
Function:	noun
Etymology:	alteration of mimeme, from _mim- _(as in mimesis) + -eme
1: an idea, behavior, style, or usage that spreads from person to person within a culture
[Source]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carbondale</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/08/22/carbondale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/08/22/carbondale/</guid>
      <description>Made for a long day
Driving home from Carbondale
Bugs splat like popcorn</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#define prostitot</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/06/02/define-prostitot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/06/02/define-prostitot/</guid>
      <description>A young girl dressed in hooker wear, a la Britney, Christina, etc.
[Source]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#define sorostitute</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/06/02/define-sorostitute/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/06/02/define-sorostitute/</guid>
      <description>A physically attractive female who looks as if she may belong to a sorority, while at the same time being dressed like a complete slut. A true sorostitute would wear a low-cut halter top and a short, tight skirt in the middle of wintertime.
[Source]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitty soup!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/30/kitty-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/30/kitty-soup/</guid>
      <description>I got some more of the disposable cameras from the wedding processed. Nothing too interesting aside from a few shots of the cats I took to use up film that I&amp;rsquo;ve put up in the usual place. Here are a couple of highlights:

Merry likes to play in the laundry
Spooky likes to play in the big soup pot Silly kitties! And now that my folks have come to visit the grand-kitties (don&amp;rsquo;t ask&amp;hellip; I didn&amp;rsquo;t coin the phrase), they have all sorts of new cat toys to play with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best blog ever!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/12/best-blog-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/12/best-blog-ever/</guid>
      <description>Ran across the best blog ever this afternoon. The Daily Kitten! Go there. NOW!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#define &#34;prairie restoration project&#34;</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/10/define-prairie-restoration-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/10/define-prairie-restoration-project/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve seen a few of these around town. Apparently the park district is spinning them as restoring some of the land controlled by the park district to it&amp;rsquo;s original &amp;ldquo;prairie&amp;rdquo; condition. In practice, I think this largely translates to &amp;ldquo;um, this is too much work, so we&amp;rsquo;re just going to stop mowing some of these and put up a sign.&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve always found the park district to be rather interesting around here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate/Government Parodies on the Web</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/28/corporategovernment-parodies-on-the-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/28/corporategovernment-parodies-on-the-web/</guid>
      <description>Saw this Slashdot post. A student at CMU made a website parodying the Wal-Mart Foundation (a thinly veiled attempt to improve the parent corp&amp;rsquo;s public image through small scattered donations) for a class on &amp;ldquo;Parasitic Media&amp;rdquo;. Guess Wal-Mart didn&amp;rsquo;t take too kindly to how they were portrayed, so they whipped out that horrendous piece of legeslation, the Digital Millenium Copyright Act (DMCA). The DMCA&amp;rsquo;s a vague wording allows large corporations with lots of cash to easily threaten things they don&amp;rsquo;t like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hedberg</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/07/hedberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/07/hedberg/</guid>
      <description>Apparently the comic Mitch Hedberg died Wednesday, March 30th, 2005. Cause of death was heart failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silly kitties!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/02/15/silly-kitties/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/02/15/silly-kitties/</guid>
      <description>Our kitties are silly! Apparently, one of our fuzzy blankets reminds Spooky an awful lot of his mama, because he&amp;rsquo;s taken to kneading, suckling, and lapping on it. I was petting him this morning (in an attempt to keep him from completely waking me up) when he started in on the blanket. He had to be going at that thing for at least half an hour. Silly kitty.
Even worse&amp;hellip; Miss Merry was getting a little old when we adopted her, but I thought vaccinations should be top priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Song Lyrics</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/26/song-lyrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/26/song-lyrics/</guid>
      <description>Got a couple of song lyrics related websites for you. I rarely have a clue what the artist/author means when they create something, be it abstract painting, poetry, or song lyrics. So I found songmeanings.net of some interest. On a related note, have you ever heard little kids singing a song (or the pledge of allegience). As a group, they usually sound about right, but if you listen to them individually, you hear some rather bizarre stuff that sounds about right, but is totally wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitch Hedberg</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/12/mitch-hedberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/12/mitch-hedberg/</guid>
      <description>So in my Christmas stocking this year I got a Mitch Hedberg CD, Strategic Grill Locations. I&amp;rsquo;d seen him on Comedy Central some time back and found him absolutely hilarious. He&amp;rsquo;s got this funny, stoner sort of vibe and just cranks out all sorts of oddball, inane comments that are really entertaining. If you are a follower of my blog, you may have already noticed that I have a number of his quotes that randomly appear in the sidebar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disgruntled Clown</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/20/disgruntled-clown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/20/disgruntled-clown/</guid>
      <description>So last weekend (not yesterday but a week before that) Amanda and I went to Bloomington to meet up with a couple of her friends from work to go see a comedy show. It was held in a dive bar (didn&amp;rsquo;t seem all that bad by campus bar standards, but it definitely wasn&amp;rsquo;t a ritzy comedy club either), and featured the Disgruntled Clown. He&amp;rsquo;s the &amp;ldquo;ex-ex-stepfather&amp;rdquo; of one of Amanda&amp;rsquo;s friends (we&amp;rsquo;re not quite sure what&amp;rsquo;s meant by the ex-ex- part&amp;hellip; not the last ex-stepfather, but the one before that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scariest thing</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/14/scariest-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/14/scariest-thing/</guid>
      <description>Saw the scariest thing on my drive into work today. Was at a stoplight behind a giant yellow schoolbus&amp;hellip; with a big &amp;ldquo;STUDENT DRIVER&amp;rdquo; sign on the back. Eek! Watching them try to make a turn didn&amp;rsquo;t make me ever want to put my kid on a schoolbus. Ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitties!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/02/kitties/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/02/kitties/</guid>
      <description>So slashdot had an interesting IT review link today: Juvenile felis catus (or &amp;ldquo;kitten&amp;rdquo; for you laymen). Full of very cute pictures, a lot of tongue-in-cheek commentary, and links to all sorts of amusing/geeky/just plain weird sites (standard kitten package and CAT Users&#39; Manual). Oh, and he even provides a convenient summary comparison against competing models (i.e. puppies, babies, or a new video card). Now that Amanda and I have a house, we&amp;rsquo;ll get to start looking for kittens before long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebToons: Angry Alien</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/19/webtoons_angry_alien/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/19/webtoons_angry_alien/</guid>
      <description>Angry Alien has a series of WebToons that are popular movies in 30 seconds&amp;hellip; re-enacted by bunnies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebToons: Happy Tree Friends</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/19/webtoons_happy_tree_friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/19/webtoons_happy_tree_friends/</guid>
      <description>Who can forget the Happy Tree Friends when they&amp;rsquo;re talking about bizarre little WebToons? The series consists of a bunch of shorts of little cute fuzzy animals meeting their demise in a disturbing manner. Fun for the whole family. I also ran across this site that appeared to have all of the episodes available for convenient viewing (I don&amp;rsquo;t think the official site has all of the older ones). These toons have even come out on DVD if you can believe it (that&amp;rsquo;s how I first saw them).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leather?</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/02/leather/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/08/02/leather/</guid>
      <description>Ok. So I was poking around Gamestop, and ran across this. Can you believe it? For those of you who just couldn&amp;rsquo;t get enough leather, a leather computer mouse?
Anyway, I can&amp;rsquo;t wait till Doom 3 hits shelves, hopefully tomorrow. Now I just have to wait for Half-Life 2, which looks awesome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleh</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/27/bleh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/27/bleh/</guid>
      <description>Derek brain stopped. Derek need lunch. Derek need talk in third person. Derek should be president. Derek tired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ebay Auctions: Tools and ...?</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/15/ebay_auctions_tools_and_/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/15/ebay_auctions_tools_and_/</guid>
      <description>So, can anyone tell me what&amp;rsquo;s not quite right about this ebay store?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponge Monkeys!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/06/15/sponge_monkeys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/06/15/sponge_monkeys/</guid>
      <description>So I ran across this post over at adland about the Quiznos Sponge Monkeys. I&amp;rsquo;ve been wondering where on earth they came up with those brilliant, bizarre, singing critters. So freakin&#39; hilarious. Anyway, the ads are done by this guy as demonstrated by this other webshort of his about the moon. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t look like everyone over at adland appreciates them though&amp;hellip; since they seem to have confused the little furry critters with rats which they don&amp;rsquo;t think are appropriate in food ads&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Predictor</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/19/job_predictor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/19/job_predictor/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a silly little webpage I Richy clued me into. It supposedly predicts your ideal career based on your name (since it&amp;rsquo;s probably based on some sort of hash function or something, inclusion of middle and/or last name may improve your career path). For example:
 Derek, Your ideal jobs is a Kids TV Presenter Derek Gottlieb, Your ideal job is a Bearded Lady in the circus. Derek Brendan Gottlieb, Your ideal job is a Office numpty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebToons: Amy Winfrey</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/19/webtoons_amy_winfrey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/19/webtoons_amy_winfrey/</guid>
      <description>So recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching some webtoons done by Amy Winfrey (works as an animator for South Park), and they&amp;rsquo;re pretty cute. I started watching her current toon, Making Fiends, that revolves around two little girls, Vendetta and Charlotte, who go to school together. Vendetta makes all sorts of fiends and attempts to intimidate and destroy Charlotte, while Charlotte&amp;rsquo;s busy making friends. That led me to her previous set of toons, MuffinFilms, which are a variety of short animations involving muffins.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
