<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>music on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in music on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/music/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>eMusic makes me a sad panda</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2009/06/15/emusic-makes-me-a-sad-panda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2009/06/15/emusic-makes-me-a-sad-panda/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been a happy happy joy joy subscriber at eMusic since 2005. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure what I thought initially when Lee clued me into it (indie music being a new thing for me), but after that first month I was hooked. Took me a few months and then I bumped up to the annual subscription option. Until recently, my most recent subscription plan worked out to $16/month, which got me 90 tracks a month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All things must end...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/11/11/all-things-must-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/11/11/all-things-must-end/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been expecting to hear this for a while, but it&amp;rsquo;s still a bummer to find out that The Reputation have officially broken up. In Elizabeth&amp;rsquo;s words:
As I&amp;rsquo;m guessing many of you have already figured out, the band is over.
Sean quit. Rest of us just gave up, I guess. I don&amp;rsquo;t currently have plans to do any more music or play any more shows. Breaks my fucking heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Reputation et al @ the Courtyard Cafe, Illini Union</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/08/28/the-reputation-et-al-the-courtyard-cafe-illini-union/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/08/28/the-reputation-et-al-the-courtyard-cafe-illini-union/</guid>
      <description>Rachel came down to visit this past weekend and we caught the show at the Courtyard Cafe Saturday night. I was really wanting to catch Elizabeth Elmore again with the rest of her band, The Reputation, and had heard they were to go on third which in theory would be around 10:30. Not wanting to miss them, I figured we should get there by 10 just to be sure, and probably got there a fair bit before that since we caught the tail end of the first act, Judah Johnson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Elmore Solo @ the Courtyard Cafe, Illini Union</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/08/26/elizabeth-elmore-solo-the-courtyard-cafe-illini-union/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/08/26/elizabeth-elmore-solo-the-courtyard-cafe-illini-union/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking forward to it for a few weeks since I read about it, and managed to catch Elizabeth Elmore playing solo at the Courtyard Cafe in the Union. Free show no less. There were pretty clearly only a handful of people that were explicitly there to attend the show and an assortment of others that were there just eating their lunch or studying or what-not. Good show though. Just her and her electric (Gibson SG I believe).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Karma</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/28/bad-karma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/28/bad-karma/</guid>
      <description>I guess I&amp;rsquo;ve been swimming in bad karma or something lately. First, I broke the nice set of Sennheiser HD515 cans I use at work leaving me with the craptacular closed Aiwas I&amp;rsquo;d used before seeing the light. Then, I broke the belt clip on my cellphone. Fortunately, superglue seems to have solved both problems.
Then, I realized my Thinkpad wasn&amp;rsquo;t charging like it should. Everything indicated it was charging, but the battery meter kept getting lower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damn Dolphins!... or hanging out with Rachel and Tammy</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/24/damn-dolphins-or-hanging-out-with-rachel-and-tammy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/24/damn-dolphins-or-hanging-out-with-rachel-and-tammy/</guid>
      <description>Rachel and her roommate Tammy (who&amp;rsquo;s a hoot btw) came down Friday night to catch the show at the Canopy Club featuring The Living Blue, Tractor Kings, Dark Country, and The Dolphin. We showed up some time during the Dolphin&amp;rsquo;s set and all I have to say is weird. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really tell whether they were playing something or just getting setup and making random noises on-stage. We elected to wait out at the bar until after their set was over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have it on good authority that...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/07/i-have-it-on-good-authority-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/07/i-have-it-on-good-authority-that/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Indie rock is coming to town.&amp;rdquo; :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is Grand</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/03/12/this-is-grand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/03/12/this-is-grand/</guid>
      <description>Lee and I trekked up to Chicago to catch The New Pornographers / Belle &amp;amp; Sebastian play at the Riviera Friday night.
I handled travel plans (directions to the Park&amp;amp;Ride; station where we parked and caught the &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rdquo;, trains to take, transfers to make, how to get to the theater, last train we&amp;rsquo;d have to catch). Pretty uneventful trip for the most part. The most interesting part was how the bike lane to the side of the road in Chicago was used as a thug passing lane by many.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The violin&#39;s never been so cool...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/02/04/another-day-another-concert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/02/04/another-day-another-concert/</guid>
      <description>Caught Andrew Bird last night with Lee at the Canopy Club. Impressive live show. I was really amazed how much can come out of so few people. If you&amp;rsquo;ve never heard Andrew Bird, his music has lots going on. Very melodic. The show (and presumably his album too) was performed by two people using slick audio equipment. They&amp;rsquo;d play several measures on one instrument, loop it, then play along to it with other stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I love indie music!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/01/21/i-love-indie-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/01/21/i-love-indie-music/</guid>
      <description>Finally got to see The Reputation live&amp;hellip; and they rocked! Went to see them last night with Lee at Cowboy Monkey here in CU and they were fantastic. Great show. Can&amp;rsquo;t beat the price either. $8 cover for 3 bands playing a 45 minute set each. And Lee and I were right up there by the stage. Couldn&amp;rsquo;t get much closer without completely losing my hearing. :) A good time was definitely had by all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bummer... Missing The Reputation Again</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/11/29/bummer-missing-the-reputation-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/11/29/bummer-missing-the-reputation-again/</guid>
      <description>Was just poking around online last night and realized The Reputation is playing in town again next week at the Canopy Club. And unfortunately I&amp;rsquo;ve also realized Amanda and I are going to a Madrigal dinner at ISU in Bloomington that same night. Oh well. I&amp;rsquo;ll get to see them some day I hope. :(</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies, Music, and Birthdays Oh My!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/11/28/movies-music-and-birthdays-oh-my/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/11/28/movies-music-and-birthdays-oh-my/</guid>
      <description>Took a vacation of sorts down to SoFlo (hey, SoCal&amp;rsquo;s accepted, why not SoFlo for the sunshine state?) with Amanda to visit the folk this past week for Thanksgiving and Birthdays and so forth. Really spent a fair portion of my time going through the crap in my room from my childhood. Not so fun and I&amp;rsquo;m surprised Amanda didn&amp;rsquo;t kill me for wasting her limited vacation time in this manner, but at least we got to go to Monkey Jungle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mobiBLU DAH-1500i</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/09/01/mobiblu-dah-1500i/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/09/01/mobiblu-dah-1500i/</guid>
      <description>So I broke down and bought a new mp3 player to take with me when I go jogging&amp;hellip; well jogging/walking&amp;hellip; well really more walking than jogging, but I&amp;rsquo;m still building up toward that. Anyway, looks like it should be a pretty cute little unit. Key features:
It&amp;rsquo;s about a 1&amp;quot; cube has a little OLED display comes in 256MB, 512MB, and 1GB versions (I got the 512) has an FM radio (can even record it at up to 160kbps) 8-10 hours of battery life when playing mp3s USB2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CU Music, Parasol and Angie</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/25/cu-music-parasol-and-angie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/25/cu-music-parasol-and-angie/</guid>
      <description>A while back Lee clued me into eMusic, a cool indie music mp3 site (subscription based, but their high-quality, mp3s unencumberd by any crappy drm). Managed to stumble over Angie Heaton who has a few albums out. Was listening to her when Amanda asked me who that was&amp;hellip; when I told her, she said Rachel had listened to her. I took that as a cue to ask Rachel what she listened to next time I saw her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing tunes on OS X</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/12/playing-tunes-on-os-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/12/playing-tunes-on-os-x/</guid>
      <description>So it would seem that the release of iTunes by Apple largely killed off the other music playing apps (ie mp3 players). Which is lame because I find the interface a little bulky, doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem like I can have it sort based on directory structure, and I find it a little annoying that by default it wants to copy all of your music to a &amp;ldquo;My Music&amp;rdquo; type folder when you import new stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Song Lyrics</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/26/song-lyrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/26/song-lyrics/</guid>
      <description>Got a couple of song lyrics related websites for you. I rarely have a clue what the artist/author means when they create something, be it abstract painting, poetry, or song lyrics. So I found songmeanings.net of some interest. On a related note, have you ever heard little kids singing a song (or the pledge of allegience). As a group, they usually sound about right, but if you listen to them individually, you hear some rather bizarre stuff that sounds about right, but is totally wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MP3 Players</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/26/mp3-players/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/26/mp3-players/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve been drooling over new MP3 players recently. There&amp;rsquo;s been all sorts of activity in iPod-land. You&amp;rsquo;ve got the 4th gen iPods that bump battery life up to ~12 hours per charge. You&amp;rsquo;ve got the U2 Special Edition iPod that comes in a snazzy black color scheme with a sharply contrasting red click-wheel, band member autographs engraved on the back, and a $50 iTunes coupon good toward the purchase of &amp;ldquo;The Complete U2&amp;rdquo; (I&amp;rsquo;m guessing that only partially covers the price of admission, and isn&amp;rsquo;t all that great a deal since they&amp;rsquo;ve bumped up the price of the unit by $50).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evanescence: DI Photo</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/10/evanescence_di_photo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/10/evanescence_di_photo/</guid>
      <description>Looks like the DI did actually send a photographer to the Evanescence concert&amp;hellip; they just never bothered to publish a story or any photos about it until now. Basically, they&amp;rsquo;ve got a feature on the DI Finest Photos of 2004 (little presumptuous seeing as the year&amp;rsquo;s not even half over). But apparently, they thought this photo of Evanescence was one of their best of the year. Why it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have warranted publishing earlier on that basis, I don&amp;rsquo;t know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Folds followup</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/07/ben_folds_followup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/07/ben_folds_followup/</guid>
      <description>So Richy had some nice news for me. Turns out somebody managed to get a high quality bootleg of Monday&amp;rsquo;s concert up by Tuesday afternoon. Quality&amp;rsquo;s quite good, so you may want to check it out. Also, Richy&amp;rsquo;s got his pictures up from the concert now. You can see them here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Folds</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/06/ben_folds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/06/ben_folds/</guid>
      <description>So Amanda and I (along with Richy, Carrie, Lee, and Dan) went to the Ben Folds concert last night at Foellinger. The show was great! The opening act was a great string trio led by David Berkeley on guitar, and assisted by Will Robertson on upright bass and Adam Buchwald(?) on mandolin. They were really good. I loved the mix of the 3 instruments. You should definitely check out David Berkeley if you get the chance (there&amp;rsquo;s a mp3 available for download on his page of a song &amp;ldquo;Fire Sign&amp;rdquo; that was featured in CBS&amp;rsquo; show Without a Trace).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evanescence</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/02/26/evanescence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/02/26/evanescence/</guid>
      <description>So I saw Evanescence in concert this past Tuesday at the Assembly Hall. Great show.
First opening act, Atomship, was kinda eh. They weren&amp;rsquo;t awful, but they certainly weren&amp;rsquo;t very good either. Lead singer was pretty weird. Had something vaguely resembling a British accent until he mentioned they were from Mississippi when he suddenly reverted to a good ol&#39; boy accent. And he had this weird twitchy, seizurey sort of &amp;ldquo;dance&amp;rdquo; thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liz Phair followup</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/12/02/liz_phair_followup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/12/02/liz_phair_followup/</guid>
      <description>Just wanted to post a quick followup to my previous Liz Phair post. Found this pretty cool shot of her performing at Foellinger (courtesy of the Daily Illini).
I lost count, but I believe she rotated between 3 Fender electrics and some sort of acoustic during the course of the show with her roadie retuning between swaps. She claimed she had to swap out guitars a lot because he would have to retune depending on the song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liz Phair</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/11/18/liz_phair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/11/18/liz_phair/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, so things have been pretty busy the past several months, and I haven&amp;rsquo;t made any posts here since the fall semester started. Anyway, just wanted to pop on here to say I went to the Liz Phair concert last night and it rocked. Quite outstanding. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard her stuff, and like &amp;ldquo;chick rock&amp;rdquo;, I&amp;rsquo;d suggest checking her out. Her most recent album is more pop than her older stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
