<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>amalgam on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/amalgam/</link>
    <description>Recent content in amalgam on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2003 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/amalgam/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Workalicious</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/03/27/workalicious/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/03/27/workalicious/</guid>
      <description>Finished the final touches on my MSE paper and uploaded it to their server. I already faxed over the copyright form, so I should be good to go to head out to Anaheim in June. Pretty sweet. I&amp;rsquo;ve got postscript and pdf versions of the paper ready to go up on my work page whenever I decide it&amp;rsquo;s appropriate to be publicly available.
The conference should prove interesting seeing as it falls smack between the abstract and paper deadlines for MICRO&amp;hellip; Hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll be in a position to worry about it at that point instead of still debugging the local data caches and getting more benchmarks up and running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work update</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/15/work_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/15/work_update/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, so I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty busy this past week, and haven&amp;rsquo;t really had time to post. Chi-Wei checked in fixes for the bulk of the bugs I had encountered in the gui, so I&amp;rsquo;m pretty happy. I can actually sorta use the thing now. More importantly, Jeff and I have made some comments about additional features we REALLY want, so with any luck, we&amp;rsquo;ll actually get some of those before long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Beginnings of Coherency&#34; and the &#34;Mess we call a GUI&#34;</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/05/beginnings_of_coherency_and_the_mess_we_call_a_gui/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/05/beginnings_of_coherency_and_the_mess_we_call_a_gui/</guid>
      <description>So my local data caches finally started doing stuff today. Cluster 0 requests M[0x0]. The main cache sends all words in that local cache line and informs cluster 0 that it has exclusive access. Cluster 1 then requests M[0x0]. The main cache informs Cluster 0 that the block is now shared and waits for an ACK to confirm that it hasn&amp;rsquo;t become modified. Pretty sweet! I may actually have it all up and running before much longer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goals and Dreams</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/01/27/goals_and_dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/01/27/goals_and_dreams/</guid>
      <description>So Nick scheduled our first Amalgam meeting of the semester for today. But unfortunately, our meetings are scheduled for right before his class (which he has never taught before). As a result, he ditched our meeting to finish preparing his lecture. Nothing like getting things done early. Anyway, he dropped by around 1/2 hour before the meeting to tell Jeff and me that he wasn&amp;rsquo;t coming and we should figure out where the project will be around the end of the semester and what conferences we should shoot for.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
