<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>college on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/college/</link>
    <description>Recent content in college on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/college/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#define alcoholiday</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/04/define-alcoholiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/04/define-alcoholiday/</guid>
      <description>An occasion like Hallowe&amp;rsquo;en, April Fool&amp;rsquo;s, or Father&amp;rsquo;s/Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day. Though not categorized as an official holiday, is often used as a good occasion to get a good drunk on with friends.
&amp;ldquo;Shit dude! It&amp;rsquo;s Hallowe&amp;rsquo;en, my favorite alcoholiday! Let&amp;rsquo;s get done up as Zombies and get druuuuunk!!!&amp;rdquo;
[Source]
We were in CU this past weekend to close on the sale of our old house (yay!). Seems we hadn&amp;rsquo;t realized it was &amp;ldquo;Unofficial&amp;rdquo; St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As you may have noticed...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/25/as-you-may-have-noticed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/25/as-you-may-have-noticed/</guid>
      <description>Amanda and I are buying a new house. In a land far far from CU&amp;hellip; Huntsville, AL to be exact&amp;hellip; or technically Madison, AL to be even more exact (suburb to the west of Huntsville).
No, Derek didn&amp;rsquo;t graduate. While one could ask &amp;ldquo;why is he leaving sans-degree&amp;rdquo;, a better question might be &amp;ldquo;why is he referring to himself in the third person?&amp;rdquo; To put it simply, I just got fed up with how things have been going (or not going to be more precise) and decided it was time for a change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hell hath frozen over, Part III</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/14/hell-hath-frozen-over-part-iii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/14/hell-hath-frozen-over-part-iii/</guid>
      <description>Apparently the UofI hasn&amp;rsquo;t called a snow day since &amp;lsquo;79. That&amp;rsquo;s close to 30 years of no snow days. They had some silly spokesperson on the news last night that tried to claim we were such a hardy campus and liked to walk everywhere so it took an awful lot to shut us down. Apparently they decided that severe blizzard conditions with 45mph gusts and snow falling way faster than the plows could ever hope to keep up with might actually warrant a snow day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hell hath frozen over</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/13/hell-hath-frozen-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/13/hell-hath-frozen-over/</guid>
      <description>All classes have been canceled for Tuesday (Feb. 13) at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign. More than 5 inches of snow fell overnight, up to another foot of snow is possible by Tuesday night and a blizzard warning is in effect. U. of I. employees who have been designated as essential personnel are expected to report to work.
This mailing approved by: The Office of the Chancellor
The U of I never cancels class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hell hath frozen over, Continued</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/13/hell-hath-frozen-over-continued/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/13/hell-hath-frozen-over-continued/</guid>
      <description>All Wednesday (Feb. 14) classes at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign have been cancelled.
Continuing high winds and snow have made it impossible to keep streets and sidewalks clear and safe.
Only personnel providing critical services should continue to report for each work shift until further notice. Employees uncertain about their status should direct any questions to their supervisors.
Classes at the U. of I. Child Development Lab also are cancelled for Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life and ASPLOS</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/10/20/life/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/10/20/life/</guid>
      <description>So life has been pretty&amp;hellip; something recently. Too much going on and not quite enough sanity to go around. Fortunately, I get to head out to San Jose this Sunday to visit with Rich and Carrie&amp;hellip; oh yeah and go to ASPLOS (Architectural Support for Programming Languages and Operating Systems). Looks like it should be an interesting conference and the best part is I don&amp;rsquo;t have to foot the bill. :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s at it again</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/13/googles-at-it-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/13/googles-at-it-again/</guid>
      <description>Looks like their calendar solution has gone &amp;ldquo;live&amp;rdquo;. Looks like it has most of the stuff I&amp;rsquo;d like&amp;hellip; add events via web, multiple calendars, publish all info or free/busy info (or nothing), subscribing to other published calendars (such as the UIUC Academic calendar courtesy of ACM&amp;rsquo;s Macwarriors), import CSV/iCal, export XML/iCal, assorted notification options, some sort of ability to auto-add event invites, manage who you share a given calendar with (including giving them the ability to manage events).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great quote at IBM day</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/10/21/great-quote-at-ibm-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/10/21/great-quote-at-ibm-day/</guid>
      <description>Heard this great quote from the late/great Seymour Cray: &amp;ldquo;If you were plowing a field, which would you rather use: Two strong oxen or 1024 chickens?&amp;rdquo; Apparently he said this in response to a question about the growing use of large clusters of commodity PCs for supercomputing applications. Traditional wisdom would suggest it&amp;rsquo;s much better to design the heck out of two very powerful processors and ease the parallel programming burden to achieve high performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You eeediot!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/10/11/you-eeediot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/10/11/you-eeediot/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s the deal with stupid people getting union secretary gigs in Universities? Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, I&amp;rsquo;ve met some great and helpful secretaries in my time. But so many of them are just so useless! I&amp;rsquo;ve been dealing a bit with one in the business office for our department trying to place orders for my students in senior design. Here are my two experiences so far:
Took a couple of days to get my first order placed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stupid people suck!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/18/stupid-people-suck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/18/stupid-people-suck/</guid>
      <description>I hate stupid people. I can accept that the population at large is generally clueless about all things tech, and so I have a fairly high tolerance level when they do annoying newb things. The people that really tick me off are the ones who are clearly in a technical field (say, a whole bunch of people in academia on a FPGA research/education mailing list), and are clearly clueless about very basic concepts such as email&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding, wedding, and more weddings...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/30/weddings-wedding-and-more-weddings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/30/weddings-wedding-and-more-weddings/</guid>
      <description>Been rather busy lately. Went to my cousin&amp;rsquo;s wedding 3 weekends ago in Missouri/Kansas. Then flew down to Amanda&amp;rsquo;s cousin&amp;rsquo;s wedding in Texas 2 weekends ago. My folks have been visiting this past week and just left on Sunday morning. To top that off, I&amp;rsquo;ve had some sort of nasty sinus infection for the past week. Next weekend we&amp;rsquo;re off to Iowa for Amanda&amp;rsquo;s coworker&amp;rsquo;s wedding and on the way back I&amp;rsquo;ll be going to ISCA &amp;lsquo;05 in Wisconsin for a few days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UR-5beta</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/26/ur-5beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/26/ur-5beta/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to work a bit on porting over some of my old content to the new site/format. So far, I&amp;rsquo;ve converted over the pages about the senior design project I developed with John, the UR-5beta. Figure I may put up a copy of my public key at some point, but since the only one I use with any regularity is already up at my CRHC site, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure there&amp;rsquo;s much point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rant: Parking</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/09/17/rant-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/09/17/rant-parking/</guid>
      <description>So as of a few weeks ago, they finally got the parking deck close enough to &amp;ldquo;finished&amp;rdquo; to open it. By &amp;ldquo;finished&amp;rdquo;, I mean the bulk of the structure is there, but they&amp;rsquo;re still actively working on it. Like putting in the sidewalks around it, putting in the street to the south, actually building up the 1st floor interior (where all the &amp;ldquo;retail&amp;rdquo; is supposed to go). Oh, and of course installing the elevators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleh</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/27/bleh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/27/bleh/</guid>
      <description>Derek brain stopped. Derek need lunch. Derek need talk in third person. Derek should be president. Derek tired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting close...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/07/getting_close/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/07/getting_close/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;m finally getting close to wrapping up this semester, which marks the end of my required course credits. All of the stuff for Nick&amp;rsquo;s class finished up yesterday afternoon. The slides for all of the project presentations are up at the ECE497NC website. We managed to slap together something for the poster session for Matt&amp;rsquo;s class this afternoon. Went ok, but since a large portion of the project is compiler stuff, and I haven&amp;rsquo;t the remotest clue about compilers in general so&amp;hellip; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t much help in fielding questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects Galore</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/07/projects_galore/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/07/projects_galore/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve been going nuts working on class projects this semester. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to wrap up the last of my class work and am currently taking a couple of ECE497 courses (special topics grad courses where professors largely discuss their own research interests).
Nick&amp;rsquo;s teaching one on Unconventional Computer Architecture that&amp;rsquo;s been pretty interesting so far. Project&amp;rsquo;s coming along pretty well for that and most of my responsibilities have been finished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logic Simulator</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/17/logic_simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/17/logic_simulator/</guid>
      <description>After a little bit of work, I got the simulation of 32 input vectors in parallel up and running in my simulator. Pretty sweet. Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be too bad to get basic sequential circuit support added in and then I&amp;rsquo;ll have done both extra credit options. Mainly need to figure out how to time my program and the rest is trivial. Will probably look into doing some further optimizing of my code, but seems pretty zippy for any circuit I&amp;rsquo;ve run it on so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work update</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/15/work_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/15/work_update/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, so I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty busy this past week, and haven&amp;rsquo;t really had time to post. Chi-Wei checked in fixes for the bulk of the bugs I had encountered in the gui, so I&amp;rsquo;m pretty happy. I can actually sorta use the thing now. More importantly, Jeff and I have made some comments about additional features we REALLY want, so with any luck, we&amp;rsquo;ll actually get some of those before long.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
