<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/categories/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/categories/general/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Linkage: MuchoSucko</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/07/linkage_muchosucko/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/07/linkage_muchosucko/</guid>
      <description>Just ran across an interesting site. Appears to be a collection of oddball videos and such that have surfaced on the net. For example, there&amp;rsquo;s this vid of a kid going after a pi?ata, and news footage of a helicopter crash (always figured they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be pretty with those giant spinning blades). Note: definitely not work safe stuff here (there&amp;rsquo;s some non kid-friendly stuff there&amp;hellip;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies I&#39;ve written about...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/19/movies_ive_written_about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/19/movies_ive_written_about/</guid>
      <description>So I borrowed some movies from Richy this past weekend (namely Jurassic Park, The Lost World, Batman, and Batman Returns). It reminded me just how good Jurassic Park was. Heck, I even used a quote from it in my high school yearbook (you ever look back at that sort of stuff and wonder what you were thinking&amp;hellip; all sorts of really meaningful/significant quotes you can put in there, and I put in something from a fairly silly hollywood flick).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding stuff</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/18/wedding_stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/18/wedding_stuff/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a good portion of the weekend working on getting wedding invites/response cards printed up on my old laser. Not to toot my own horn, but I think they turned out pretty cool. The font Amanda used (A Yummy Apology) went really well with her watercolor flowers and the deckled edges on the paper (scares me that I know what that means). Anyway, they&amp;rsquo;re pretty cool and should be spooling up to send them all out before much longer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Year Anniversary</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/28/1_year_anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/28/1_year_anniversary/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the one year anniversary of the day I broke my leg. Now for a moment of silence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fuali tests</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/23/fuali_tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/23/fuali_tests/</guid>
      <description>Took some tests at Fuali.com. Here are my results:
I am 29% Geek
You probably work in computers, or a history deptartment at a college. You never really fit in with the &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo; crowd. But you have friends, and this is a good thing.
I am 37% Internet Addict
I could go either way. Deep into the madness of nights filled with coding CGI-Scripts and online role playing games, or I could become a normal user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little more of Gel than Jeff was expecting...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/20/a_little_more_of_gel_than_jeff_was_expecting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/20/a_little_more_of_gel_than_jeff_was_expecting/</guid>
      <description>Had an entertaining conversation with Jeff yesterday. Somehow we got on the topic of ECE291 and his team project. And how most of the rest of his team was pretty worthless. Anyway, he googled himself and showed me the webpage that the team made for their project. Turns out Gel (from IMSA) was on his team. So we started talking about her. So I guess Jeff was getting a little peeved by his team members and wasn&amp;rsquo;t convinced they were putting any effort into the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day after V-Day</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/15/day_after_v-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/02/15/day_after_v-day/</guid>
      <description>So, yesterday was Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day. I think I managed to succeed at being all sweet and romantical by surprising Amanda by making her lasagna from scratch with a side of garlic bread. Turned out pretty well considering I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really following any particular recipe. Also got her a copy of &amp;ldquo;My Big Fat Greek Wedding&amp;rdquo; and a set of cute dragonfly chopsticks from ArtMart. Oh, and of course a cute little card with a whole bunch of lady bugs that form a heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weblinks?</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/01/25/weblinks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/01/25/weblinks/</guid>
      <description>Time to try out some things in this new weblog thingamadoo. Can I make links, such as this one to the UCA webpage? Or one to the Amalgam webpage?
More importantly, why am I up at this ungodly hour on a Saturday?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
