<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dandelion Day on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/dandelion-day/atom/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dandelion Day on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/dandelion-day/atom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>#define alcoholiday</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/04/define-alcoholiday</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/04/define-alcoholiday</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An occasion like Hallowe&amp;rsquo;en, April Fool&amp;rsquo;s, or Father&amp;rsquo;s/Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day. Though not categorized as an official holiday, is often used as a good occasion to get a good drunk on with friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Shit dude! It&amp;rsquo;s Hallowe&amp;rsquo;en, my favorite alcoholiday! Let&amp;rsquo;s get done up as Zombies and get druuuuunk!!!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=alcoholiday&#34;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were in CU this past weekend to close on the sale of our old house (yay!).  Seems we hadn&amp;rsquo;t realized it was &amp;ldquo;Unofficial&amp;rdquo; St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day at the UofI.  If you aren&amp;rsquo;t from the CU area, you&amp;rsquo;re probably not aware of this particular alcoholiday.  Seems several years back, Cochrane (the beer baron of campus, owning 10 of the major campus bars) decided he was missing out on a lot of income since St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day typically fell during spring break and thus students weren&amp;rsquo;t taking that opportunity to drink heavily in his establishments.  So he instituted &amp;ldquo;Unofficial&amp;rdquo;, which comes a couple of weeks before spring break so that students can ditch class on a Friday and get trashed all day long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In some sense, stuff like this just seems like it&amp;rsquo;s part of the college experience, but it makes campus a little crazy for those that aren&amp;rsquo;t choosing to partake.  For example, Amanda and I wanted to go to Papa Del&amp;rsquo;s while we were in town because you just can&amp;rsquo;t get anything resembling good Chicago-style deep dish pizza in Huntsville.  I&amp;rsquo;d talked to some folks about meeting there on Friday night, only to find out it was Unofficial.  Since we didn&amp;rsquo;t really want to fight our way through all that, we figured we&amp;rsquo;d go to Pasha for some Mediterranean and hit Papa Del&amp;rsquo;s up on Saturday night.  Talking to some friends, we found out Cochrane realized he was still not making enough money, so he went ahead and extended it a two day party starting this year.  So Saturday was out too.  Fortunately Sunday night worked out though, so we did get our pizza fix.  I&amp;rsquo;m waiting for the day I hear they&amp;rsquo;ve extended Unofficial to be a week-long thing like Mardi Gras.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sample coverage of this year&amp;rsquo;s activities: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.news-gazette.com/news/local/2008/03/01/not_everyone_celebrates_alcoholiday&#34;&gt;Not everyone celebrates alcoholiday&amp;hellip;&lt;/a&gt; (News-Gazette)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be honest, this isn&amp;rsquo;t the first college-wide booze party I&amp;rsquo;ve come into contact with.  While I was at the University of Rochester, there was a day-long party known as Dandelion Day, or more commonly D-Day.  Another example of students getting up earlier than they normally would in order to get thoroughly trashed by 10am.  Managed to dig up a &lt;a href=&#34;http://media.www.campustimes.org/media/storage/paper371/news/2004/04/22/Features/The-History.Of.DDay-668430.shtml&#34;&gt;History of D-Day&lt;/a&gt; that gives a bit more background than I can.  Talks about how things were substantially toned down during the 90&amp;rsquo;s with stuff about no open containers.  As things typically work, this translated into &amp;ldquo;you can&amp;rsquo;t walk around the quad with an open beer bottle in your hand, but if you pour your beer/hard liquor into a plastic cup, you&amp;rsquo;re good to go.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>