<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>illinois on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/illinois/</link>
    <description>Recent content in illinois on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/illinois/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Christmas snow in Illinois</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/01/07/christmas-snow-in-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/01/07/christmas-snow-in-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Finally getting around to going through photos I&amp;rsquo;ve taken recently and uploaded a set I took of the snow while we were in Champaign for Christmas. Here&amp;rsquo;s a sample that I liked with Sarah chasing Rachel down the street with a snow shovel full of snow:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#define alcoholiday</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/04/define-alcoholiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/04/define-alcoholiday/</guid>
      <description>An occasion like Hallowe&amp;rsquo;en, April Fool&amp;rsquo;s, or Father&amp;rsquo;s/Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day. Though not categorized as an official holiday, is often used as a good occasion to get a good drunk on with friends.
&amp;ldquo;Shit dude! It&amp;rsquo;s Hallowe&amp;rsquo;en, my favorite alcoholiday! Let&amp;rsquo;s get done up as Zombies and get druuuuunk!!!&amp;rdquo;
[Source]
We were in CU this past weekend to close on the sale of our old house (yay!). Seems we hadn&amp;rsquo;t realized it was &amp;ldquo;Unofficial&amp;rdquo; St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas, Movie-House!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/12/25/merry-christmas-movie-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/12/25/merry-christmas-movie-house/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s that time of year. Time to watch favorites like &amp;ldquo;How the Grinch Stole Christmas&amp;rdquo; (the real one, not that live-action debacle starring Jim Carrey and directed by Ron Howard) and &amp;ldquo;A Christmas Story&amp;rdquo; (they looked at me like i had lobsters crawling out of my ears!). Seems like Christmas has rushed up to me before I had a chance to notice. Fortunately I was able to get the little bit of shopping I wanted to do done yesterday, and no it wasn&amp;rsquo;t nearly as bad as I had feared.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blizzard pics &#39;07</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/15/blizzard-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/15/blizzard-pics/</guid>
      <description>Took some pictures of the snow yesterday and put them up on flickr:

We definitely got a fair bit of snow, and some of the drifts were pretty impressive. Unfortunately, the winds and the city plows concentrated and packed the snow on our side of the street (but it did mean our street was plowed a few times as opposed to the more minor streets that maybe saw one pass&amp;hellip; benefits of being a city and school bus route).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hell hath frozen over, Part III</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/14/hell-hath-frozen-over-part-iii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/14/hell-hath-frozen-over-part-iii/</guid>
      <description>Apparently the UofI hasn&amp;rsquo;t called a snow day since &amp;lsquo;79. That&amp;rsquo;s close to 30 years of no snow days. They had some silly spokesperson on the news last night that tried to claim we were such a hardy campus and liked to walk everywhere so it took an awful lot to shut us down. Apparently they decided that severe blizzard conditions with 45mph gusts and snow falling way faster than the plows could ever hope to keep up with might actually warrant a snow day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hell hath frozen over</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/13/hell-hath-frozen-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/13/hell-hath-frozen-over/</guid>
      <description>All classes have been canceled for Tuesday (Feb. 13) at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign. More than 5 inches of snow fell overnight, up to another foot of snow is possible by Tuesday night and a blizzard warning is in effect. U. of I. employees who have been designated as essential personnel are expected to report to work.
This mailing approved by: The Office of the Chancellor
 The U of I never cancels class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hell hath frozen over, Continued</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/13/hell-hath-frozen-over-continued/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/13/hell-hath-frozen-over-continued/</guid>
      <description>All Wednesday (Feb. 14) classes at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign have been cancelled.
Continuing high winds and snow have made it impossible to keep streets and sidewalks clear and safe.
Only personnel providing critical services should continue to report for each work shift until further notice. Employees uncertain about their status should direct any questions to their supervisors.
Classes at the U. of I. Child Development Lab also are cancelled for Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All things must end...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/11/11/all-things-must-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/11/11/all-things-must-end/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been expecting to hear this for a while, but it&amp;rsquo;s still a bummer to find out that The Reputation have officially broken up. In Elizabeth&amp;rsquo;s words:
 As I&amp;rsquo;m guessing many of you have already figured out, the band is over.
Sean quit. Rest of us just gave up, I guess. I don&amp;rsquo;t currently have plans to do any more music or play any more shows. Breaks my fucking heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Reputation et al @ the Courtyard Cafe, Illini Union</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/08/28/the-reputation-et-al-the-courtyard-cafe-illini-union/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/08/28/the-reputation-et-al-the-courtyard-cafe-illini-union/</guid>
      <description>Rachel came down to visit this past weekend and we caught the show at the Courtyard Cafe Saturday night. I was really wanting to catch Elizabeth Elmore again with the rest of her band, The Reputation, and had heard they were to go on third which in theory would be around 10:30. Not wanting to miss them, I figured we should get there by 10 just to be sure, and probably got there a fair bit before that since we caught the tail end of the first act, Judah Johnson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Elmore Solo @ the Courtyard Cafe, Illini Union</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/08/26/elizabeth-elmore-solo-the-courtyard-cafe-illini-union/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/08/26/elizabeth-elmore-solo-the-courtyard-cafe-illini-union/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking forward to it for a few weeks since I read about it, and managed to catch Elizabeth Elmore playing solo at the Courtyard Cafe in the Union. Free show no less. There were pretty clearly only a handful of people that were explicitly there to attend the show and an assortment of others that were there just eating their lunch or studying or what-not. Good show though. Just her and her electric (Gibson SG I believe).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holy crap!  Do you think he failed?</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/05/16/holy-crap-do-you-think-he-failed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/05/16/holy-crap-do-you-think-he-failed/</guid>
      <description>From WICD15 News:
 Champaign Drivers Test Goes Wrong
2 people are rushed to the hospital after a driver crashes through a window at the Department of Motor Vehicles In Champaign.
The 27-year-old man taking his driving test.
One person inside was hit.
And the instructor, riding in that car, was also hurt.
 Apparently the guy drove all the way into the waiting area. Like ALL the way. I thought this stuff was reserved for South Floridians&amp;hellip; And is it just me, or is that a really strange, terse blurb the news people put on their website?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damn Dolphins!... or hanging out with Rachel and Tammy</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/24/damn-dolphins-or-hanging-out-with-rachel-and-tammy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/24/damn-dolphins-or-hanging-out-with-rachel-and-tammy/</guid>
      <description>Rachel and her roommate Tammy (who&amp;rsquo;s a hoot btw) came down Friday night to catch the show at the Canopy Club featuring The Living Blue, Tractor Kings, Dark Country, and The Dolphin. We showed up some time during the Dolphin&amp;rsquo;s set and all I have to say is weird. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really tell whether they were playing something or just getting setup and making random noises on-stage. We elected to wait out at the bar until after their set was over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s at it again</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/13/googles-at-it-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/13/googles-at-it-again/</guid>
      <description>Looks like their calendar solution has gone &amp;ldquo;live&amp;rdquo;. Looks like it has most of the stuff I&amp;rsquo;d like&amp;hellip; add events via web, multiple calendars, publish all info or free/busy info (or nothing), subscribing to other published calendars (such as the UIUC Academic calendar courtesy of ACM&amp;rsquo;s Macwarriors), import CSV/iCal, export XML/iCal, assorted notification options, some sort of ability to auto-add event invites, manage who you share a given calendar with (including giving them the ability to manage events).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is Grand</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/03/12/this-is-grand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/03/12/this-is-grand/</guid>
      <description>Lee and I trekked up to Chicago to catch The New Pornographers / Belle &amp;amp; Sebastian play at the Riviera Friday night.
I handled travel plans (directions to the Park&amp;amp;Ride; station where we parked and caught the &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rdquo;, trains to take, transfers to make, how to get to the theater, last train we&amp;rsquo;d have to catch). Pretty uneventful trip for the most part. The most interesting part was how the bike lane to the side of the road in Chicago was used as a thug passing lane by many.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The violin&#39;s never been so cool...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/02/04/another-day-another-concert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/02/04/another-day-another-concert/</guid>
      <description>Caught Andrew Bird last night with Lee at the Canopy Club. Impressive live show. I was really amazed how much can come out of so few people. If you&amp;rsquo;ve never heard Andrew Bird, his music has lots going on. Very melodic. The show (and presumably his album too) was performed by two people using slick audio equipment. They&amp;rsquo;d play several measures on one instrument, loop it, then play along to it with other stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I love indie music!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/01/21/i-love-indie-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/01/21/i-love-indie-music/</guid>
      <description>Finally got to see The Reputation live&amp;hellip; and they rocked! Went to see them last night with Lee at Cowboy Monkey here in CU and they were fantastic. Great show. Can&amp;rsquo;t beat the price either. $8 cover for 3 bands playing a 45 minute set each. And Lee and I were right up there by the stage. Couldn&amp;rsquo;t get much closer without completely losing my hearing. :) A good time was definitely had by all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bummer... Missing The Reputation Again</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/11/29/bummer-missing-the-reputation-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/11/29/bummer-missing-the-reputation-again/</guid>
      <description>Was just poking around online last night and realized The Reputation is playing in town again next week at the Canopy Club. And unfortunately I&amp;rsquo;ve also realized Amanda and I are going to a Madrigal dinner at ISU in Bloomington that same night. Oh well. I&amp;rsquo;ll get to see them some day I hope. :(</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great quote at IBM day</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/10/21/great-quote-at-ibm-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/10/21/great-quote-at-ibm-day/</guid>
      <description>Heard this great quote from the late/great Seymour Cray: &amp;ldquo;If you were plowing a field, which would you rather use: Two strong oxen or 1024 chickens?&amp;rdquo; Apparently he said this in response to a question about the growing use of large clusters of commodity PCs for supercomputing applications. Traditional wisdom would suggest it&amp;rsquo;s much better to design the heck out of two very powerful processors and ease the parallel programming burden to achieve high performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OTR architect joins the ECE department!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/10/14/otr-architect-joins-the-ece-department/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/10/14/otr-architect-joins-the-ece-department/</guid>
      <description>I should really pay closer attention to who joins our department. Nikita Borisov apparently just started here this semester and is currently doing work on anonymous peer-to-peer networks. Nick introduced him to Jeff and I today with the intention of giving him some of our spare computers to get his group started.
Afterwards I took a look at his past work and realized he was one of the primary architects for Off-the-Record Messaging that I use in Gaim (Linux/Windows) and AdiumX (OSX).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You eeediot!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/10/11/you-eeediot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/10/11/you-eeediot/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s the deal with stupid people getting union secretary gigs in Universities? Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, I&amp;rsquo;ve met some great and helpful secretaries in my time. But so many of them are just so useless! I&amp;rsquo;ve been dealing a bit with one in the business office for our department trying to place orders for my students in senior design. Here are my two experiences so far:
 Took a couple of days to get my first order placed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carbondale</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/08/22/carbondale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/08/22/carbondale/</guid>
      <description>Made for a long day
Driving home from Carbondale
Bugs splat like popcorn</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CU Music, Parasol and Angie</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/25/cu-music-parasol-and-angie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/25/cu-music-parasol-and-angie/</guid>
      <description>A while back Lee clued me into eMusic, a cool indie music mp3 site (subscription based, but their high-quality, mp3s unencumberd by any crappy drm). Managed to stumble over Angie Heaton who has a few albums out. Was listening to her when Amanda asked me who that was&amp;hellip; when I told her, she said Rachel had listened to her. I took that as a cue to ask Rachel what she listened to next time I saw her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago photos</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/13/chicago-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/13/chicago-photos/</guid>
      <description>Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve uploaded bits and pieces of the Chicago photos (still not quite done sifting through the stuff from the Field Museum or any of my skyline/downtown shots or those in Millenium Park). You can check them out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Museum Goodness</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/12/chicago-museum-goodness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/12/chicago-museum-goodness/</guid>
      <description>Amanda and I just got back last night from a long weekend trip up to Chicago. Headed up there Friday morning and hit the Shedd Aquarium, apparently oldest aquarium in the country (founded 75 years ago). Since we were planning on hitting lots of museums, we picked up &amp;ldquo;city passes&amp;rdquo; that include admission to a number of different sites in the area (if you see more than two of the six, I think you made out well).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding, wedding, and more weddings...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/30/weddings-wedding-and-more-weddings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/30/weddings-wedding-and-more-weddings/</guid>
      <description>Been rather busy lately. Went to my cousin&amp;rsquo;s wedding 3 weekends ago in Missouri/Kansas. Then flew down to Amanda&amp;rsquo;s cousin&amp;rsquo;s wedding in Texas 2 weekends ago. My folks have been visiting this past week and just left on Sunday morning. To top that off, I&amp;rsquo;ve had some sort of nasty sinus infection for the past week. Next weekend we&amp;rsquo;re off to Iowa for Amanda&amp;rsquo;s coworker&amp;rsquo;s wedding and on the way back I&amp;rsquo;ll be going to ISCA &amp;lsquo;05 in Wisconsin for a few days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#define &#34;prairie restoration project&#34;</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/10/define-prairie-restoration-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/10/define-prairie-restoration-project/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve seen a few of these around town. Apparently the park district is spinning them as restoring some of the land controlled by the park district to it&amp;rsquo;s original &amp;ldquo;prairie&amp;rdquo; condition. In practice, I think this largely translates to &amp;ldquo;um, this is too much work, so we&amp;rsquo;re just going to stop mowing some of these and put up a sign.&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve always found the park district to be rather interesting around here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OBO at it again: 9mm raffle</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/14/obo-at-it-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/14/obo-at-it-again/</guid>
      <description>Looks like the Orange and Blue Observer (OBO) are at it again. When I went to drop off my Rentertainment DVDs today, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but notice the sidewalk chalk ads everywhere for a 9mm raffle being held today on the Quad. Guess their AK-47 raffle went well enough that they decided to make some more money (and presumably make some sort of statement at the same time).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AK-47 raffle?</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/03/30/ak-47-raffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/03/30/ak-47-raffle/</guid>
      <description>Was accosted by a guy on the quad yesterday about the strangest fundraiser I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen on a college campus. This guy was selling raffle tickets to win an AK-47&amp;hellip; presumably a functional one. Didn&amp;rsquo;t probe to see if he was raising money for some &amp;ldquo;cause&amp;rdquo; or if he just had it lying around and wanted more beer money. Weird!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raiders</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/30/raiders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/30/raiders/</guid>
      <description>Went to the Castle Theater in Bloomington yesterday with Amanda to see Raiders of the Lost Ark. Really outstanding theater setup. Instead of the usual uncomfortable, cramped stadium seating, the Castle has a set of squishy couches and loveseats. Much more enjoyable experience. Raiders is such a classic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rant: Parking</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/09/17/rant-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/09/17/rant-parking/</guid>
      <description>So as of a few weeks ago, they finally got the parking deck close enough to &amp;ldquo;finished&amp;rdquo; to open it. By &amp;ldquo;finished&amp;rdquo;, I mean the bulk of the structure is there, but they&amp;rsquo;re still actively working on it. Like putting in the sidewalks around it, putting in the street to the south, actually building up the 1st floor interior (where all the &amp;ldquo;retail&amp;rdquo; is supposed to go). Oh, and of course installing the elevators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPS?</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/15/gps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/15/gps/</guid>
      <description>So earlier this week I noticed they had added an LED array display inside every bus. Reason I noticed this is because one of them was randomly displaying some info. Most of it was debugging stuff. What&amp;rsquo;s the version number of this unit, how much memory does it have, what time/day is it (which was totally wrong), etc. You get the idea. Occasionally, it would scroll street intersection info across the screen (like &amp;ldquo;PROSPECT AND KIRBY&amp;rdquo;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evanescence: DI Photo</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/10/evanescence_di_photo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/05/10/evanescence_di_photo/</guid>
      <description>Looks like the DI did actually send a photographer to the Evanescence concert&amp;hellip; they just never bothered to publish a story or any photos about it until now. Basically, they&amp;rsquo;ve got a feature on the DI Finest Photos of 2004 (little presumptuous seeing as the year&amp;rsquo;s not even half over). But apparently, they thought this photo of Evanescence was one of their best of the year. Why it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have warranted publishing earlier on that basis, I don&amp;rsquo;t know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Folds followup</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/07/ben_folds_followup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/07/ben_folds_followup/</guid>
      <description>So Richy had some nice news for me. Turns out somebody managed to get a high quality bootleg of Monday&amp;rsquo;s concert up by Tuesday afternoon. Quality&amp;rsquo;s quite good, so you may want to check it out. Also, Richy&amp;rsquo;s got his pictures up from the concert now. You can see them here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Folds</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/06/ben_folds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/04/06/ben_folds/</guid>
      <description>So Amanda and I (along with Richy, Carrie, Lee, and Dan) went to the Ben Folds concert last night at Foellinger. The show was great! The opening act was a great string trio led by David Berkeley on guitar, and assisted by Will Robertson on upright bass and Adam Buchwald(?) on mandolin. They were really good. I loved the mix of the 3 instruments. You should definitely check out David Berkeley if you get the chance (there&amp;rsquo;s a mp3 available for download on his page of a song &amp;ldquo;Fire Sign&amp;rdquo; that was featured in CBS&#39; show Without a Trace).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evanescence</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/02/26/evanescence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/02/26/evanescence/</guid>
      <description>So I saw Evanescence in concert this past Tuesday at the Assembly Hall. Great show.
First opening act, Atomship, was kinda eh. They weren&amp;rsquo;t awful, but they certainly weren&amp;rsquo;t very good either. Lead singer was pretty weird. Had something vaguely resembling a British accent until he mentioned they were from Mississippi when he suddenly reverted to a good ol&#39; boy accent. And he had this weird twitchy, seizurey sort of &amp;ldquo;dance&amp;rdquo; thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liz Phair followup</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/12/02/liz_phair_followup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/12/02/liz_phair_followup/</guid>
      <description>Just wanted to post a quick followup to my previous Liz Phair post. Found this pretty cool shot of her performing at Foellinger (courtesy of the Daily Illini).
I lost count, but I believe she rotated between 3 Fender electrics and some sort of acoustic during the course of the show with her roadie retuning between swaps. She claimed she had to swap out guitars a lot because he would have to retune depending on the song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liz Phair</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/11/18/liz_phair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/11/18/liz_phair/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, so things have been pretty busy the past several months, and I haven&amp;rsquo;t made any posts here since the fall semester started. Anyway, just wanted to pop on here to say I went to the Liz Phair concert last night and it rocked. Quite outstanding. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard her stuff, and like &amp;ldquo;chick rock&amp;rdquo;, I&amp;rsquo;d suggest checking her out. Her most recent album is more pop than her older stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
