<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>chicago on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/chicago/</link>
    <description>Recent content in chicago on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/chicago/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This is Grand</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/03/12/this-is-grand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/03/12/this-is-grand/</guid>
      <description>Lee and I trekked up to Chicago to catch The New Pornographers / Belle &amp;amp; Sebastian play at the Riviera Friday night.
I handled travel plans (directions to the Park&amp;amp;Ride; station where we parked and caught the &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rdquo;, trains to take, transfers to make, how to get to the theater, last train we&amp;rsquo;d have to catch). Pretty uneventful trip for the most part. The most interesting part was how the bike lane to the side of the road in Chicago was used as a thug passing lane by many.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago photos</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/13/chicago-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/13/chicago-photos/</guid>
      <description>Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve uploaded bits and pieces of the Chicago photos (still not quite done sifting through the stuff from the Field Museum or any of my skyline/downtown shots or those in Millenium Park). You can check them out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Museum Goodness</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/12/chicago-museum-goodness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/12/chicago-museum-goodness/</guid>
      <description>Amanda and I just got back last night from a long weekend trip up to Chicago. Headed up there Friday morning and hit the Shedd Aquarium, apparently oldest aquarium in the country (founded 75 years ago). Since we were planning on hitting lots of museums, we picked up &amp;ldquo;city passes&amp;rdquo; that include admission to a number of different sites in the area (if you see more than two of the six, I think you made out well).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
