<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>photography on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/photography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in photography on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/tags/photography/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Baby Eleanora</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2012/11/16/baby-eleanora/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2012/11/16/baby-eleanora/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://farm9.staticflickr.com/8054/8120790185_2a8829e0c7_n.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Baby Nora&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Adelaide is here!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/11/20/baby-adelaide-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/11/20/baby-adelaide-is-here/</guid>
      <description>Surprise! We&amp;rsquo;d been up to Vanderbilt for our last clinic visit before the planned c-section and had just finished our tour of L&amp;amp;D; and were walking to the car to head home when baby Adelaide must&amp;rsquo;ve decided she liked the place so much she wanted to stay. Amanda&amp;rsquo;s water broke and so we went right back in and now baby Addy&amp;rsquo;s here! She was born @ 13:01 on the 17th and weighed in at a healthy 6 lbs 11 oz at 19 1/w inches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alabama faux-snow</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/01/07/alabama-faux-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/01/07/alabama-faux-snow/</guid>
      <description>As a followup to my snow photos from Champaign at Christmas, here&amp;rsquo;s a sample of a few photos documenting what it takes to shutdown much of Huntsville:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas snow in Illinois</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/01/07/christmas-snow-in-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2010/01/07/christmas-snow-in-illinois/</guid>
      <description>Finally getting around to going through photos I&amp;rsquo;ve taken recently and uploaded a set I took of the snow while we were in Champaign for Christmas. Here&amp;rsquo;s a sample that I liked with Sarah chasing Rachel down the street with a snow shovel full of snow:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nashville Photos: Lane Motor Museum</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/05/03/nashville-photos-lane-motor-museum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/05/03/nashville-photos-lane-motor-museum/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago, we went up to Nashville and hit a number of the sights. I&amp;rsquo;ll go ahead and split this into two posts, since I&amp;rsquo;ve only uploaded some of the relevant photos so far. The first day, we hit their recreation of the Parthenon. Apparently, it&amp;rsquo;s actually the second replica they&amp;rsquo;ve built, with the first being built in 1897 to celebrate their centennial but it was only built to last 6 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More photos from Savannah trip: Museum of Aviation</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/23/more-photos-from-savannah-trip-museum-of-aviation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/23/more-photos-from-savannah-trip-museum-of-aviation/</guid>
      <description>On the drive back from Savannah, Charles and I quickly stopped in to visit the Robins Air Force Base Museum of Aviation. Didn&amp;rsquo;t spend very long there, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t too much out of the way for the drive back and had a chance to take a few pics. There were some more unusual planes there that I&amp;rsquo;d meant to go back and look up info on, but obviously hadn&amp;rsquo;t since I only just pulled the photos off my camera a few days ago with the rest of the photos from Savannah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space &amp; Rocket Center</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/23/space-rocket-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/23/space-rocket-center/</guid>
      <description>Finally caught up with going through my photos and uploading to Flickr. Katie was in town visiting this past week (Spring Break). Aside from the holy week activities (choir tired now), one afternoon Amanda and I took off work and all three of us went to the Space &amp;amp; Rocket Center. Lots of interesting historical NASA stuff (early V-2 rockets, Saturn V/Apollo stuff, etc), but I have to admit some of it felt a bit slapped together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Savannah</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/19/savannah/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2008/03/19/savannah/</guid>
      <description>Took a trip for work back in December to provide cluster training for some of the engineers at Gulfstream. Seems like we also did some very minor maintenance on the cluster we administer there. Anyway, I brought the camera along and had a chance to take a few pics while wandering around the riverfront. Only got around to pulling them off my camera today, so here they are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More photos from Alabama: Cathedral Caverns, Autumn at Monte Sano, and pumpkins</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/12/16/more-photos-from-alabama-cathedral-caverns-autumn-at-monte-sano-and-pumpkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/12/16/more-photos-from-alabama-cathedral-caverns-autumn-at-monte-sano-and-pumpkins/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m finally getting around to sifting through some of the photos I&amp;rsquo;ve taken over the past couple of months and uploading them to Flickr. Here&amp;rsquo;s the one from the first batch taken at Cathedral Caverns in Scottsboro, AL:
And here are some shots I took of the Autumn trees from up on Monte Sano:
And a few shots of our pumpkins from Halloween:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo usage</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/30/photo-usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/30/photo-usage/</guid>
      <description>Apparently it&amp;rsquo;s been a busy week for my flickr photos. I&amp;rsquo;ve had two that were selected for inclusion in various web things.
First, one of my Ireland honeymoon photos was selected for inclusion in Schmap Dublin Third Edition (check out Literary Dublin: Trinity College). Oddly enough, it was a photo I took while we were wandering around Trinity College. Here&amp;rsquo;s a little descriptive blurb from their website:
Exploring a Schmap Guide is a uniquely interactive experience: maps and guide content are dynamically integrated, allowing intuitive, real-time access to reviews and photo slideshows for places of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As you may have noticed...</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/25/as-you-may-have-noticed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/07/25/as-you-may-have-noticed/</guid>
      <description>Amanda and I are buying a new house. In a land far far from CU&amp;hellip; Huntsville, AL to be exact&amp;hellip; or technically Madison, AL to be even more exact (suburb to the west of Huntsville).
No, Derek didn&amp;rsquo;t graduate. While one could ask &amp;ldquo;why is he leaving sans-degree&amp;rdquo;, a better question might be &amp;ldquo;why is he referring to himself in the third person?&amp;rdquo; To put it simply, I just got fed up with how things have been going (or not going to be more precise) and decided it was time for a change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huntsville and such</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/05/10/huntsville-and-such/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/05/10/huntsville-and-such/</guid>
      <description>Those of you who know me should know why I haven&amp;rsquo;t updated in a long time. Amanda and I had a very long month when we went down to Huntsville for Mike&amp;rsquo;s wedding. We had our baby Isaac prematurely, and after fighting for three long weeks in the Huntsville NICU, he passed away peacefully in our arms. We&amp;rsquo;re still having a hard time with it, but I suppose it&amp;rsquo;s good to talk about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blizzard pics &#39;07</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/15/blizzard-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/02/15/blizzard-pics/</guid>
      <description>Took some pictures of the snow yesterday and put them up on flickr:
We definitely got a fair bit of snow, and some of the drifts were pretty impressive. Unfortunately, the winds and the city plows concentrated and packed the snow on our side of the street (but it did mean our street was plowed a few times as opposed to the more minor streets that maybe saw one pass&amp;hellip; benefits of being a city and school bus route).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Diary, caught sleeping</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/15/cat-diary-caught-sleeping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/15/cat-diary-caught-sleeping/</guid>
      <description>Boss kitty caught me sleeping again. Don&amp;rsquo;t know why he makes such a big deal about it. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t everyone sleep like their dead?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Diary, Day 752</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/15/cat-diary-day-752/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2007/01/15/cat-diary-day-752/</guid>
      <description>Day 752 of my captivity. Found what I hope is one of my captor&amp;rsquo;s favorite possessions. It appears to be some sort of container for transporting instruments of my exploitation and I believe it to be associated with their obnoxious light flashing device.
I have thoroughly inspected it&amp;rsquo;s contents to ascertain if it might hold anything I could use in my escape. Having found nothing, I destroyed it&amp;rsquo;s lining with my claws and ate the outer edges to prevent its further use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Fran and Pumpkins</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/10/30/san-fran-and-pumpkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/10/30/san-fran-and-pumpkins/</guid>
      <description>Have some pics up from my trip to the bay area up at Flickr:
Was a good trip overall. Real good to see Richy and Carrie and get to hang out with them some and see some sights. Got up to the Golden Gate bridge, although didn&amp;rsquo;t see that much since it was really foggy. Headed down to the Fisherman&amp;rsquo;s Wharf and wandered around there for a while checking out the sea lions and Ghirardelli and such.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some more Sammy and Spooky pics</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/08/img_1953jpg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/04/08/img_1953jpg/</guid>
      <description>IMG_1953.JPG
Originally uploaded by derekgottlieb.
Uploaded some new kitty pictures to flickr. Some cute pics of Sammy lounging in the laundry hamper and Spooky lounging on our bed. Spooky&amp;rsquo;s getting so big!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitty part trois</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/02/22/kitty-part-trois/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2006/02/22/kitty-part-trois/</guid>
      <description>We adopted our third kitty this past Saturday thanks to Amanda&amp;rsquo;s sister Katie. She&amp;rsquo;d found him as a stray hanging around the house of some of her boyfriend&amp;rsquo;s friends down in Carbondale. Seems there&amp;rsquo;s a BIG stray cat problem down in that neck of the woods (presumably because of all the college students in the area, and their decision to ditch their cats when they move). I think the call she made to Amanda about the kitty went something like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago photos</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/13/chicago-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/13/chicago-photos/</guid>
      <description>Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve uploaded bits and pieces of the Chicago photos (still not quite done sifting through the stuff from the Field Museum or any of my skyline/downtown shots or those in Millenium Park). You can check them out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flickr</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/03/flickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/07/03/flickr/</guid>
      <description>This is a test post from , a fancy photo sharing thing.
Pretty cool. Looks like flickr will let you upload 20M of photos per month, and makes the last 200 you&amp;rsquo;ve posted visible. Has assorted useful features such as tagging photos, controlling who can see photos, etc. Seems pretty cool. I might just use it some for more temporary stuff (ie stuff I don&amp;rsquo;t want to archive on the web forever and take up precious space on my webhost).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitty soup!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/30/kitty-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/05/30/kitty-soup/</guid>
      <description>I got some more of the disposable cameras from the wedding processed. Nothing too interesting aside from a few shots of the cats I took to use up film that I&amp;rsquo;ve put up in the usual place. Here are a couple of highlights:
Merry likes to play in the laundry
Spooky likes to play in the big soup pot Silly kitties! And now that my folks have come to visit the grand-kitties (don&amp;rsquo;t ask&amp;hellip; I didn&amp;rsquo;t coin the phrase), they have all sorts of new cat toys to play with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cardboard sculpture (followup)</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/27/cardboard-sculpture-followup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/27/cardboard-sculpture-followup/</guid>
      <description>Talked about this earlier. Managed to take some more pictures today and actually load them onto my computer (as opposed to deleting them accidently again. In addition to Optimus Prime, there were several milk carton people (only took a picture of one, but may go back for more later), a giant fork (didn&amp;rsquo;t take a picture because I wasn&amp;rsquo;t as enthralled by it, and it looked like it was slightly broken), a burning foosball player, and a really bizarre one involving a giant beetle pushing a dirt clod with a human fetus inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Older kitty pics</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/26/older-kitty-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/26/older-kitty-pics/</guid>
      <description>Finally got around to loading up some of my older kitty pics that were on my other camera. They start off with Spooky attacking Space Chicken when he was a little bitty kitten, and moves on to the cats playing with each other and a box.
On a related note, I did take my camera in to work today, and I did take pictures of the cardboard sculptures in Beckman. Unfortunately, when I went to download them onto my computer I accidently deleted them instead of downloading them (bit of a usability issue with Picasa IMHO).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry&#39;s trip to the vet (aka a little snip-snip)</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/08/merrys-trip-to-the-vet-aka-a-little-snip-snip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/04/08/merrys-trip-to-the-vet-aka-a-little-snip-snip/</guid>
      <description>Dropped Merry off at the vet this morning for spaying (finally). Leaving her there all alone (overnight no less) really pulled at my heartstrings. :( I&amp;rsquo;m such a softie. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how parents manage to drop their kids off at school for the first time.
On a related note, I finally got around to uploading some more kitty pictures. Been having hardware problems with my CompactFlash reader (took forever to get it to mount, took forever to get a directory listing, took forever to transfer the files, and some of the files were corrupted by the time they got to my computer).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitty part deux</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/11/kitty-part-deux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2005/01/11/kitty-part-deux/</guid>
      <description>We adopted our second kitty this past Sunday. He is an adorable 8-week old black and white kitten. He&amp;rsquo;s predominantly black with a little white stripe down his nose, a white chin and tummy, and white paws. As per the suggestion of his previous home (one of Amanda&amp;rsquo;s co-workers), we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to call him Spooky. I kept thinking of the X-Files (Fox &amp;ldquo;Spooky&amp;rdquo; Mulder), and he seems to spook pretty easily for a kitty as curious and fearless as he appears to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/28/christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/28/christmas/</guid>
      <description>Had a good Christmas this year. My folks came up the Tuesday before XMas and stayed at the new house till they left this past Sunday (ie Amanda and I ran out and bought a 2nd bed the weekend before they got here). Had a pretty good visit with them and got a chance to get my Dad&amp;rsquo;s input on some household projects.
We opened our presents to each other (Amanda, my folks, and myself) Christmas Eve&amp;hellip; my folks and Amanda liked the panoramic photos I got from LaPayne Photography (thanks Rachel!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LBB</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/20/lbb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/20/lbb/</guid>
      <description>So it seems LBB (that&amp;rsquo;s Little Boy Blazejack) has finally come into his own. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know him, he&amp;rsquo;s the &amp;ldquo;little&amp;rdquo; brother of someone I went to high school with. Those of us who knew him always wondered if he would eventually find himself gainfully employed and at the same time doing something he enjoyed. Last I knew, I think he was getting ready to graduate from the University of Hawaii with a major in photojournalism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Printer</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/17/photo-printer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/17/photo-printer/</guid>
      <description>Well, I finally broke down and bought myself a photo printer.
I&amp;rsquo;d been surviving until recently with a close to 10 year old, increasingly finicky laser printer. It&amp;rsquo;s served me well, but I&amp;rsquo;ve had paper feed issues with it for quite some time (ie years) and have been somewhat limited by its inability to make pretty color prints and its dismal speed (did I mention it was an old parallel port model).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long overdue</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/01/long-overdue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/12/01/long-overdue/</guid>
      <description>So this update is long overdue. I&amp;rsquo;ve been really busy recently with&amp;hellip; well, life. First there was the big annual ISCA crunch where I helped Jim get his submission from 0 to paper in less than a week. Part of that was help getting him up and running on NCSA&amp;rsquo;s Itanium-2 cluster (Teragrid) so that he could have results to write about. The other part was helping him get an actual paper together the day of the deadline since Nick was focused on the other project he wanted to submit for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wood Floors</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/11/10/wood-floors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/11/10/wood-floors/</guid>
      <description>Mmmm. Wood floors. Got solid oak installed downstairs over the past couple of days. Really looks outstanding. I&amp;rsquo;ve got a bunch of pics up at the usual place, but they simply don&amp;rsquo;t do it justice. If you have a chance to come see, do so! :) Got an estimate for putting ceramic tile in the kitchen and bathrooms, and replacing the rest of the carpet (stairs and upstairs hall/bedrooms) with new carpet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House Updates</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/11/05/house-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/11/05/house-updates/</guid>
      <description>Making progress again on the house (and remembered to bring my camera again too). A bunch of the double-paned windows that had broken seals were replaced on Tuesday (turns out some of the remaining windows were misordered and the sliding glass door is on backorder). Big improvement on the ones that have been replaced though. Will actually be able to look out the windows now. Got the light green paint up on two of the walls in the dining room (but not the overhang near the cathedral ceiling), gold along the north wall with the big picture window in the living room and the sliding glass door in the dining room that leads to the deck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progress on the House</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/13/progress-on-the-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/13/progress-on-the-house/</guid>
      <description>Amanda and I have been pretty busy since we closed on the house. We&amp;rsquo;ve looked at flooring some, and I&amp;rsquo;ve started the ball rolling on fixing the windows (several of the double panes had broken seals). We&amp;rsquo;ve also done a fair bit of painting, sanding, staining, sealing, spackling, de-wallpapering, cleaning, landscaping&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to keep a pretty good photo log of our progress over in the gallery. Basically, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a full tour of the house as it was at closing, and then a separate album tracking our progress in each room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New House</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/01/new-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/10/01/new-house/</guid>
      <description>So, Amanda and I closed on the new house yesterday morning. We&amp;rsquo;re already starting to feel like homeowners. And by that, I mean we&amp;rsquo;ve already started tearing the place apart. :) For those that are interested, I&amp;rsquo;ve got some pictures up over in the gallery (taken with the new Digital Rebel).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>With a Rebel Yell!</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/09/16/digital-rebel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/09/16/digital-rebel/</guid>
      <description>Yay! My Digital Rebel just got here!!
To recap, I finally decided to break down and get myself something fun for getting my thesis deposited. Decided last week that I&amp;rsquo;d get myself a Canon Digital Rebel EOS-300D if I could find it at a price I liked. Ended up getting it at a pretty decent price ($200-250 off what I could get it for locally). Looks like it should be a pretty sweet camera ([Review, Another).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ireland Photos</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/01/ireland_photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2004/07/01/ireland_photos/</guid>
      <description>I think I&amp;rsquo;ve got the bulk of the photos from our honeymoon in Ireland cleaned up and uploaded. You should be able to view them now here. I tried setting it up to auto-resize them when I uploaded (since I don&amp;rsquo;t have the disk space to store them all full res), but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I want them any bigger than it&amp;rsquo;s currently set to. If you&amp;rsquo;ve got any feedback in that respect, please let me know.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
