<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tales of the Weird on Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/categories/tales-of-the-weird/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tales of the Weird on Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/categories/tales-of-the-weird/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Jane Story: Tupperware</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/08/14/a_jane_story_tupperware/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/08/14/a_jane_story_tupperware/</guid>
      <description>So State Farm, or at least the actuarial department, has a policy that co-workers do not bring in food to help you celebrate your birthday (or any other celebration-worthy event). That would be dumb since you end up having to bring in food frequently in a large department. State Farm&amp;rsquo;s solution: the person celebrating is expected to bring in food for the department in order to celebrate. That way, you only need to bring in food once a year (ie your own birthday).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Jane Story: Jane vs. UPS</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/08/07/a_jane_story_jane_vs_ups/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/08/07/a_jane_story_jane_vs_ups/</guid>
      <description>Well, since I&amp;rsquo;ve introduced Amanda&amp;rsquo;s co-worker Jane, I suppose I should actually start posting some of the more absurd stories about her. The first one that comes to mind I will entitle &amp;ldquo;Jane vs. UPS.&amp;rdquo;
One day, Jane got it into her head to send a marinated steak to a priest friend of hers in New Jersey. So she packaged up this piece of raw, marinated steak in a bowl surrounded by ice, and put this bowl in a box and taped it shut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tales of the Weird</title>
      <link>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/08/04/tales_of_the_weird/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thoughts.derekgottlieb.com/blog/2003/08/04/tales_of_the_weird/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to add a new category. I think I&amp;rsquo;ll title it &amp;ldquo;Tales of the Weird&amp;rdquo;, but for some reason I suspect simply &amp;ldquo;Jane Stories&amp;rdquo; would be more accurate. As such, I&amp;rsquo;ll start this category off with a brief introduction to Jane.
For those not in the know, Jane is one of Amanda&amp;rsquo;s co-workers over at State Farm corporate in Bloomington. Anyway, Jane is a weird little critter that should have been fired long ago, but somehow due to the ineptitude present in corporate America, continues to be paid to occupy space.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
